<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
	<meta type="array">
		<description>Texts for plugin 'newloginbox'</description>
		<type></type>
		<csh_table></csh_table>
		<labelContext type="array">
		</labelContext>
	</meta>
	<data type="array">
		<languageKey index="default" type="array">
			<label index="ll_welcome_header">User login</label>
			<label index="ll_welcome_message">Enter your username and password here in order to log in on the website:</label>
			<label index="ll_logout_header">You have logged out.</label>
			<label index="ll_logout_message">You just logged out from your user session on this website. You can login again or as another user by the form below.</label>
			<label index="ll_error_header">Login failure</label>
			<label index="ll_error_message">An error occurred during login. Most likely you didn't enter the username or password correctly.
Be certain that you enter them precisely as they are, including upper/lower case.
Another possibility is that cookies might be disabled in your web browser.</label>
			<label index="ll_success_header">Login successful</label>
			<label index="ll_success_message">You are now logged in as '###USER###'</label>
			<label index="ll_status_header">Current status</label>
			<label index="ll_status_message">This is your current status:</label>
			<label index="cookie_warning">Warning: There is a possibility that cookies are not enabled in your web browser! If your login disappears on your next click that is the case and you should enable cookies (or accept cookies from this website) immediately!</label>
			<label index="username">Username:</label>
			<label index="password">Password:</label>
			<label index="login">Login</label>
			<label index="permalogin">Stay logged in:</label>
			<label index="logout">Logout</label>
			<label index="send_password">Send password</label>
			<label index="reset_password">Reset Password</label>
			<label index="ll_change_password_header">Change your password</label>
			<label index="ll_change_password_message">Please enter your new password twice. Password needs a minimum length of %s chars.</label>
			<label index="ll_change_password_nolinkprefix_message">Error: there is no prefix for the link. Please set one of the following in your typoscript template: plugin.tx_felogin_pi1.feloginBaseURL = http://yourdomain/, config.baseURL = http://yourdomain/, config.absRelPrefix = http://yourdomain/</label>
			<label index="ll_change_password_notvalid_message">The link you clicked is not valid. Please repeat the forgot message procedure.</label>
			<label index="ll_change_password_notequal_message">The passwords are not equal, please enter your new password twice. Password needs a minimum length of %s chars.</label>
			<label index="ll_change_password_tooshort_message">The password length is too short. Please enter your new password twice. Password needs a minimum length of %s chars.</label>
			<label index="ll_change_password_done_message">Your password has been saved. You can now login with your new password.</label>
			<label index="change_password">Change your password</label>
			<label index="newpassword_label1">Enter new password</label>
			<label index="newpassword_label2">Repeat new password</label>
			<label index="your_email">Your email:</label>
			<label index="ll_forgot_header">Forgot your password?</label>
			<label index="ll_forgot_email_password">Your password
Hi %s

Your username is &quot;%s&quot;
Your password is &quot;%s&quot;
			</label>
			<label index="ll_forgot_email_nopassword">Your password
Hi %s

We couldn't find a username for this email address and so cannot send the password to you. Probably you misspelled the email address (upper/lower case makes a difference) or maybe you even didn't register yet?
			</label>
			<label index="ll_forgot_validate_reset_password">Your new password
Dear %s,

This email was sent in response to your request to reset your password. Please click on the link below. 
%s

For security reasons, this link is only active until %s. If you do not visit the link before then, you will need to repeat the password reset steps.
			</label>
			<label index="ll_forgot_message">Please enter the email address by which you registered your user account. Then press &quot;Send password&quot; and your password will immediately be emailed to you. Make sure to spell your email address correctly.</label>
			<label index="ll_forgot_message_emailSent">Your password has now been sent to the email address %s</label>
			<label index="ll_forgot_reset_message">Please enter your username or email address. Instructions for reseting the password will be immediately emailed to you.</label>
			<label index="ll_forgot_reset_message_emailSent">An email has been sent to the address stored in your account and contains a link to reset your password. If you do not receive an email, your account or email address was not found.</label>
			<label index="ll_forgot_header_backToLogin">Return to login form</label>
			<label index="ll_enter_your_data">Username or email address:</label>
		</languageKey>
	</data>
</T3locallang>
