<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
	<meta type="array">
		<description>CSH for Filemounts table</description>
		<type>CSH</type>
		<fileId>EXT:lang/locallang_csh_sysfilem.php</fileId>
		<csh_table>sys_filemounts</csh_table>
		<labelContext type="array">
		</labelContext>
	</meta>
	<data type="array">
		<languageKey index="default" type="array">
			<label index=".description">Filemounts describe a filepath on the server, relative or absolute.</label>
			<label index=".details">By creating a file mount record and placing a reference to it in a Backend usergroup you can allow a user access to the file mount in the File&gt;List module.
You need to create and set at least one filemount with a folder '_temp_' in it if you want users to upload files through the webbrowser.
Filemounts may also configure access to a path on the server to which the user has FTP-access. Just remember to set file-permissions on the server correctly so the webserver user (which PHP is running as) has at least read access to the FTP-dir.</label>
			<label index="_.seeAlso">be_users,
be_groups</label>
			<label index="title.description">Enter a title for the filemount</label>
			<label index="path.description">Enter the path of the filemount, relative or absolute depending on the settings of BASE.</label>
			<label index="path.details">If BASE is set to relative, the path mounted is found in the subfolder &quot;fileadmin/&quot; of the website. Then you should enter the subfolder in &quot;fileadmin/&quot; as path. For instance if you want to mount access to &quot;fileadmin/user_uploads/all/&quot; then enter the value &quot;user_uploads/all&quot; as the value of PATH.
If BASE is absolute you should enter the absolute path on the server, eg. &quot;/home/ftp_upload&quot; or &quot;C:/home/ftp_upload&quot;.

&lt;strong&gt;Notice:&lt;/strong&gt; In any case, make sure the webserver user which PHP is running as has &lt;em&gt;at least&lt;/em&gt; read-access to the path. If not, the mount will simply not appear without any warnings.
If you have problems - especially with absolute mounts - try to mount something &quot;simple&quot; like a relative path in fileadmin. If that is working well, try the absolute path.

Your PHP-configuration may also impose other restrictions on you if safe-mode like features are enabled. Then use relative paths.</label>
			<label index="_path.seeAlso">sys_filemounts:base</label>
			<label index="hidden.description">Use this option to temporarily disable the filemount.</label>
			<label index="hidden.details">All backend users using the mount will not have access anymore. This includes 'Admin'-users.</label>
			<label index="base.description">Determines whether the value of the PATH field is to be recognized as an absolute path on the server or a path relative to the fileadmin/ subfolder to the website.</label>
			<label index="_base.seeAlso">sys_filemounts:path</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="dk" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="de" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="no" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="it" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="fr" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="es" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="nl" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="cz" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="pl" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="si" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="fi" type="array">
			<label index=".description">Tiedostoasetukset (filemount) kuvaavattiedostopolkua palvelimella, relatiivista tai absoluuuttista.</label>
			<label index=".details">Luomalla tiedostoasetus tiedon ja asettamalla sen viitteeksi Tausta käyttäjäjoukolla voit antaa käyttäjäoikeuksia tiedostoasetuksille File-&gt;List aliohjelmassa.
Sinun tulee luoda vähintään yksi tiedostoasetus jossa hakemistona on '_temp_' jotta käyttäjä pystyvät myös viemään tiedostoja palvelimelle.
Tiedostoasetuksella voidaan konfiguroida ,yös polku jonne käyttäjällä on FTP-oikeus. Muista vain asettaa tiedosto-oikeudetoikein siten että www-palvelinkäyttäjä (millä PHP toimii) on vähintäin luku oikeus FTP-hakemistoon.</label>
			<label index="title.description">Anna tiedostoasetuksen (Filemount) nimi</label>
			<label index="path.description">Anna tiedostoasetusten polku, joko relatiivinen tai absoluuttinen, riippuen BASE asetuksista.</label>
			<label index="path.details">Jos Base on asetettu relatiiviseksi, voimassa oleva polku löytyy hakemiston fileadmin/ alta www-palvelimessa.
Näin ollen Sinun tulee asettaa hakemisto 'fileadmin/' poluksi. Esimerkiksi jos haluat tiedostoasetukseksi &quot;fileadmin/user_upload/all/&quot; on Sinun annettava PATH tiedoksi &quot;user_upload/all/&quot;.
Jos BASE on absoluuttinen, on Sinun annettava absoluuttinen polku palvelimessa, esim. /home/ftp_upload&quot; tai &quot;C:/home/ftp_upload&quot;.

&lt;strong&gt;Huomautus:&lt;/strong&gt; Kaikissa tapuksissa, varmista että palvelinkäyttäjä jolla PHP toimii on &lt;em&gt;ainakint&lt;/em&gt; luku-oikeudet polkuun. Jos näin ei ole, tiedostoasetukset eivät yksinkertaisesti tule näkyviin eikä varoituksia.
Jos Sinulla on ongelmia - erityisesti absoluuttisten asetusten kanssa - yrita asettaa jotain 'yksinkertaista' kuten relatiivinen asetus fileadmin hakemiston sisällä. Jos tämätoimii oikein yritä asettaa absoluuttinen polku.

Voi olla että myös PHP-asetukset aiheuttavat rajoituksia Sinulle. kuten esimerkikis safe-moodi asetukset. Käytä silloin relatiivisia asetuksia.</label>
			<label index="hidden.description">Käytä tätä vaihtoehtoa poistaaksesi tiedostoasetukset väliaikaisesti.</label>
			<label index="hidden.details">Kenelläkään taustkäyttäjälle ei ole enää oikeuksia tiedostoasetukseen. Tämä koskee myös 'Admin'-käyttäjiä.</label>
			<label index="base.description">Tällä päätellään onko PATH kentän tieto tunnistettava absoluuttiseksi vai relatiiviseksi poluksi fileadmin/ hakemiston alla olevaksi alihakemistoksi</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="tr" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="se" type="array">
			<label index=".description">Filmonteringarna visar sökvägen till en fil på servern, relativt eller absolut.</label>
			<label index=".details">By creating a file mount record and placing a reference to it in a Backend usergroup you can allow a user access to the file mount in the File&gt;List module.
You need to create and set at least one filemount with a folder '_temp_' in it if you want users to upload files through the webbrowser.
Filemounts may also configure access to a path on the server to which the user has FTP-access. Just remember to set file-permissions on the server correctly so the webserver user (which PHP is running as) has at least read access to the FTP-dir.</label>
			<label index="title.description">Fyll i en titel för filmonteringen</label>
			<label index="path.description">Fyll i filmonteringens sökväg, relativ eller absolut beroende på BASE-inställningarna.</label>
			<label index="path.details">If BASE is set to relative, the path mounted is found in the subfolder &quot;fileadmin/&quot; of the website. Then you should enter the subfolder in &quot;fileadmin/&quot; as path. For instance if you want to mount access to &quot;fileadmin/user_uploads/all/&quot; then enter the value &quot;user_uploads/all&quot; as the value of PATH.
If BASE is absolute you should enter the absolute path on the server, eg. &quot;/home/ftp_upload&quot; or &quot;C:/home/ftp_upload&quot;.

&lt;strong&gt;Notice:&lt;/strong&gt; In any case, make sure the webserver user which PHP is running as has &lt;em&gt;at least&lt;/em&gt; read-access to the path. If not, the mount will simply not appear without any warnings.
If you have problems - especially with absolute mounts - try to mount something &quot;simple&quot; like a relative path in fileadmin. If that is working well, try the absolute path.

Your PHP-configuration may also impose other restrictions on you if safe-mode like features are enabled. Then use relative paths.</label>
			<label index="hidden.description">Använd denna option för att tillfälligt stänga av filmonteringen.</label>
			<label index="hidden.details">Alla backend-användare som använder denna filmontering avstängs. Detta inkluderar också 'Admin'-användare.</label>
			<label index="base.description">Determines whether the value of the PATH field is to be recognized as an absolute path on the server or a path relative to the fileadmin/ subfolder to the website.</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="pt" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ru" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ro" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ch" type="array">
			<label index=".description">Filemounts描述在服务器上的一个文件路径,相对路径或绝对路径.</label>
			<label index=".details">在后端用户组中创建一个file mount记录并对此记录放置一个参考时,
您可以允许一个用户在文件&gt;列表模块中访问file mount.
您需要创建并设置至少一个其中带有文件夹'_temp_'的filemount,
如果您想用户通过网页浏览器上传文件.
Filemounts也可以在服务器上配置到一个路径的访问,用户有该服务
的FTP访问.只要记住在服务器上正确设置文件权限,使网站服务器
用户(运行RHP的)至少有到FTP目录的读权限.</label>
			<label index="title.description">为filemount输入一个标题</label>
			<label index="path.description">输入filemount的路径,相对路径或绝对路径取决于BASE的设置.</label>
			<label index="path.details">如果BASE设置为相对,已mount的路径在网站的子目录&quot;fileadmin/&quot; 中找到.
然后您应该在&quot;fileadmin/&quot;中输入路径子目录作为路径.例如,如果您想mount
到&quot;fileadmin/user_uploads/all/&quot;的访问,那么输入值&quot;user_uploads/all&quot;作
为路径值.
如果BASE设置为绝对,您应该在服务器上输入绝对路径,
如&quot;/home/ftp_upload&quot;或&quot;C:/home/ftp_upload&quot;.

&lt;strong&gt;注意:&lt;/strong&gt;在任何情况下,确保PHP正在运行的网站服务器
用户&lt;em&gt;至少&lt;/em&gt;有到路径的读权限.如果没有,mount将不显示并且
没有任何警告.
如果您有问题-尤其是对于绝对mounts - 试着在fileadmin中mount一些
类似于相对路径的东西.如果顺利工作的话,试一下绝对路径.

您的PHP配置可能会增强对您的限制如果象安全-模式的特性为激活.
那么使用相对路径.</label>
			<label index="hidden.description">使用此选项来暂时禁止filemount.</label>
			<label index="hidden.details">所有使用mount的后端用户将不再有访问权限.这包括'管理员'用户.</label>
			<label index="base.description">确定路径域的值是否为被识别为服务器上的一个绝对路径还是对于网站fileadmin/子目录的一个相对路径.</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="sk" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="lt" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="is" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="hr" type="array">
			<label index=".description">Poveznice (filemounts) opisuje putanju na poslužitelju, relativnu ili apsolutnu.</label>
			<label index=".details">Kreiranjem zapisa poveznice i postavljenjem reference na nju unutar pozadinske grupe korisnika možemo dozvoliti korisnicima da koriste poveznicu unutar Datoteka&gt;Popis (File&gt;List) modula.
Trebate kreirati i postaviti barem jednu poveznicu s pretincem '_temp_' ukoliko želite da korisnici mogu prenositi datoteke putem web preglednika.
Poveznice također mogu konfigurirati putanju tako da se može pristupati datotekama do kojih korisnici imaju FTP pristup. Nemojte zaboraviti postaviti dozvole nad datotekama tako da korisnik, pod čijim ovlastima je pokrenut web poslužitelj, može imati barem dozvolu čitanja.</label>
			<label index="_.seeAlso">be_korisnici,
be_grupe</label>
			<label index="title.description">Unesite naslov za poveznicu</label>
			<label index="path.description">Unesite putanju poveznice, relativnu ili apsolutnu u zavisnosti od postavljenje opcije BASE.</label>
			<label index="path.details">Ukoliko je BASE opcija postavljena kao relativna onda putanja pokazuje na potpretinac &quot;fileadmin/&quot; web sjedišta. Tada morate unjeti potpretinac unutar &quot;fileadmin/&quot; kao putanju. Na primjer želite li povezati pristup do &quot;fileadmin/user_uploads/all/&quot; onda unesite vrijednost &quot;user_uploads/all&quot; kao vrijednost putanje.
Ukoliko je BASE opcija postavljena kao apsolutna onda ptrbate unjeti apsolutnu putanju na poslužitelju, npr. &quot;/home/ftp_upload&quot; ili &quot;C:/home/ftp_upload&quot;.

&lt;strong&gt;Napomena:&lt;/strong&gt; U svakom slučaju budite sigurni da korisnik pod čijim ovlastima je pokrenut web poslužitelj ima &lt;em&gt;najmanje&gt;7em&gt; prava čitanja unesene putanje. Ukoliko nema tih prava povezani sadržaj neće se pojaviti bez ikakvih upozorenja.
Imate li problema - posebno s apsolutnim povezivanjem - pokušajete povezati nešto &quot;jednostavnije&quot; kao što je relativna ptanja unutar fileadmin pretinca. Ukoliko to radi ispravno probajte s apsolutnom putanjom.

Vaša PHP konfiguracija također može nametnuti određena ograničenja ukoliko je safe-mod ili slična značajka omogućena. Tada koristite ralativnu putanju.</label>
			<label index="_path.seeAlso">sys_filemounts:base</label>
			<label index="hidden.description">Korištenjem ove opvije privremeno onemogućavate poveznicu.</label>
			<label index="hidden.details">Svi pozadinski korisnici koriste</label>
			<label index="base.description">Određuje da li će vrijednost PATH polja biti prepoznat kao apsolutni  put na poslužitelju ili relativni put u odnosu na fileadmin/ podpretinac web sjedišta.</label>
			<label index="_base.seeAlso">sys_filemounts:path</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="hu" type="array">
			<label index=".description">A filemount egy relatív vagy abszolút file elérési utat jelent a szerveren.</label>
			<label index=".details">Egy file mount rekord készítésével és egy hivatkozás elhelyezésével egy Backend felhasználócsoportnak elérést lehet adni a file mounthoz a File&gt;Lista modulban.
Legalább egy filemount-ot kell készíteni és beállítani egy '_temp_' könyvtárral, ha azt akarod, hogy a felhasználók file-okat tudjanak feltölteni a böngészőn keresztül.
A filemount-ok elérés is biztosíthatnak egy olyan útvonalhoz a szerveren, amihez a felhasználónak van FTP elérése. Ne felejtsünk el megfelelő file-jogosultságokat adni, tehát a felhasználónak legalább olvasási joga kell hogy legyen az FTP könyvtárhoz.</label>
			<label index="title.description">Add meg a filemount nevét</label>
			<label index="path.description">Add meg a filemount elérési útját, relatív vagy abszolút módon a BASE beállításoktól függően.</label>
			<label index="path.details">Ha a BÁZIS relatívra van állítva, a mountolt útvonal a &quot;fileadmin/&quot; alkönyvtárban található. Ekkor be kell írnod a &quot;fileadmin/&quot; alkönyvtárban található elérési utyat. Tehát ha mountolni akarod a &quot;fileadmin/user_uploads/all/&quot; útvonalat, akkor &quot;user_uploads/all&quot; értéket kell az ÚTVONAL mezőbe írni.
Ha a BÁZIS abszolút, akkor a teljes szerver elérési utat be kell írni, pl. &quot;/home/ftp_upload&quot; vagy &quot;C:/home/ftp_upload&quot;.

&lt;strong&gt;Megjegyzés:&lt;/strong&gt; Figyeljünk, hogy a webszerver felhasználó, aki a PHP-t futtatja rendelkezzen &lt;em&gt;legalább&lt;/em&gt; olvasási joggal az útvonalhoz. Ha mégsem, a mount egyszerűen nem fog megjelenni, és hibaüzenetet sem küld.
Ha problémánk adódik - különösen az abszolút mount-okkal - próbáljuk valami egyszerűt mountolni, mint pl. egy relatív útvonalat a fileadmin-ban. Ha ez működik, akkor próbáljuk abszolút úttal.

A PHP beállításunk még egyéb akadályokat állíthat, ha a safe-mode típusú lehetőségek engedélyezve vannak. Ekkor használjunk relatív utakat.</label>
			<label index="hidden.description">Akkor használd, ha ideiglenesen le akarsz tiltani egy filemount-ot.</label>
			<label index="hidden.details">A mount-ot használó összes backend felhasználónak megszünt az elérése, beleértve az 'Admin' felhasználókat is.</label>
			<label index="base.description">Meghatározza, hogy a PATH mező értéke abszolút szerverútként vagy a fileadmin/ alkönyvtárhoz képest relatív módon legyen értelmezve.</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="gl" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="th" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="gr" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="hk" type="array">
			<label index=".description">檔案掛點描述一個伺服器中的路徑，相對或絕對的</label>
			<label index=".details">透過建立一個檔案掛點和在後勤使用者群組中放置一個參照，你可以許可一名使用者存取在檔案&gt;表列模組中的檔案掛點。
你需要建立和設定最少一個以 「_temp_」 的檔案掛點，假如你想使用者透過網頁溜覽器上載檔案。
檔案掛點也許同時設定對一個伺服器上的路徑的存取權限，對此使用者有 ftp 存取權限。只要緊記正確地設定伺器上的檔案存取權限，以玫網頁伺服器使用者（PHP運行時的使用者）有最基本的閱讀權限存取 FTP 資料夾。</label>
			<label index="title.description">輸入檔案掛點的名稱</label>
			<label index="path.description">輸入檔案掛點的路徑，相對的或絕對的，視乎基本的設定</label>
			<label index="path.details">假如基本設定為相對的，被掛的路徑會在網站「fileadmin」的子資料夾中。你應該輸入「fileadmin」的子資料夾為路徑。例如，你想掛上「fileadmin/user_uploads/all」的存取權，你就應該輸入「user_uploads/all」作為路徑的值。
假如基本設定是絕對的，你應該輸入伺服器上的絕對路徑，例如：「/home/ftp_upload」或「C:/home/ftp_upload」

&lt;strong&gt;留意：&lt;/strong&gt;在任何情況下，肯定網頁伺服器運行PHP的使用者有路徑&lt;em&gt;最基本&lt;/em&gt;的讀取權限。假如沒有，掛點就不會出現，而且不會沒有任何警告。
假如你有問題 - 特別是絕對掛點 - 嘗試掛入一些「簡單」，如一個在fileadmin中的相對路徑。假如運作良好，再嘗試絕對路徑。

你的 PHP 設定也許同樣會加上其他限制於你，假如啟動了類似安全模式(safe-mode)等的功能。樣就要用相對路徑。</label>
			<label index="hidden.description">使用這個選項來暫時關閉檔案掛點。</label>
			<label index="hidden.details">所有使用掛點的後勤使用者將不能存取點。包括了「管理員」使用者。</label>
			<label index="base.description">決定路徑欄的值是被看為伺服器上的絕對路徑或是一個相對於網站中fileadmin的子資料夾的路徑</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="eu" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="bg" type="array">
			<label index=".description">Файл закачването (Filemounts) описва файл пътя на сървъра, относителен или абсолютен.</label>
			<label index="title.description">Въведете име за файл закачването (filemount)</label>
			<label index="path.description">Въведете пътя на файл закачването (filemount), относителен или абсолютен в зависимост от настройките на BASE.</label>
			<label index="hidden.description">Използвайте тази опция за да изключите временно файл закачването (filemount).</label>
			<label index="hidden.details">Всички backend потребители използващи закачването (mount), няма да имат повече достъп. Това включва и 'Админ' потребителите.</label>
			<label index="base.description">Определяне дали стойността на ПЪТ (PATH) полето може да бъде разпознато като абсолютен път на сървъра или като относителен път към файладмин/ подпапка на уеб страницата.</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="br" type="array">
			<label index=".description">Pontos-de-entrada descrevem um caminho de arquivo no servidor, relativo ou absoluto.</label>
			<label index=".details">Ao criar um registro de ponto-de-entrada e colocar uma referência a ele num grupo de usuário Administrador, você pode conceder acesso ao ponto-de-entrada a um usuário no módulo Arquivo&gt;Lista.
Você deve criar ao menos um ponto-de-entrada com uma pasta '_temp_' nela se quiser que usuários sejam capazes de enviar arquivos através de um navegador web.
Pontos-de-entrada também podem configurar acesso a um caminho no servidor onde o usuário tenha acesso via FTP. Apenas lembre de criar permissões de arquivo corretamente no servidor para que o usuário do servidor (aquele que está rodando o PHP) tenha ao menos capacidade de leitura no diretório FTP.</label>
			<label index="title.description">Insira um título para o ponto-de-entrada</label>
			<label index="path.description">Insira o caminha para o ponto-de-entrada, relativo ou absoluto, dependendo das configurações da BASE.</label>
			<label index="path.details">Se BASE for configurada como relativa, o caminho montado será encontrado na subpasta &quot;fileadmin/&quot; do site. Então você deve inserir uma subpasta de &quot;fileadmin/&quot; como caminho. Por exemplo, se você quiser montar acesso para &quot;fileadmin/user_uploads/all&quot;, então insira o valor &quot;user_uploads/all&quot; como o valor de PATH.
Se BASE for absoluta, você deve inserir o caminho absoluto no servidor. Por exemplo &quot;/home/ftp_upload&quot; ou &quot;C:/home/ftp_upload&quot;.

&lt;strong&gt;Atenção:&lt;/strong&gt; Em todo caso, certifique-se de que o usuário do servidor web rodando PHP tenha &lt;em&gt;ao menos&lt;/em&gt; permissão de leitura no caminho. Se não, o ponto-de-entrada simplesmente não aparecerá, sem advertências.
Se você tiver problemas - especialmente com montagens absolutas - tente montar algo &quot;simples&quot;, como um caminho relativo em &quot;fileadmin&quot;.  Se isto funcionar corretamente, tente o caminho absoluto.

Sua configuração de PHP também pode impor outras restrições se características como 'safe-modo' estiverem habilitadas. Então use caminhos relativos.</label>
			<label index="hidden.description">Use esta opção para desativar o ponto-de-entrada temporariamente.</label>
			<label index="hidden.details">Todos os usuários-administradores usando o ponto-de-entrada não terão mais acesso a ele. Isto inclui usuários 'Admin'.</label>
			<label index="base.description">Determina se o valor do campo PATH deve ser reconhecido como um caminho absoluto no servidor ou um caminho relativo à pasta 'fileadmin/' do site.</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="et" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ar" type="array">
			<label index=".description">كمية الملفات تعبر عن عمق مسار الملف على السيرفر سواء نسبيا أو مطلقا</label>
			<label index=".details">عن طريق إنشاء سجل لملف رابط و وضعه كنقطة رجوع في مجموعة المستخدمين المصممين. و يتم ذلك عن طريق الدخول إلى الملف الرابط  في الجانب: ملف &lt; القائمة.
أنت محتاج لإنشاء على الأقل ملف رابط واحد بمجلد إسمه المجلد المؤقت '_temp_'  .</label>
			<label index="title.description">أدخل العنوان الرئيسي لرابط الملف</label>
			<label index="path.description">أدخل مسار رابط الملف سواء نسبي أو مطلق على حسب التضبيطلت الأساسية</label>
			<label index="path.details">إذا كان المسار في  الأساس معمول على مسار نسبي و المسار الرابط موجود في الملف التحتي &quot;fileadmin/&quot;   لصفحة الويب. إذاً ينبغي عليك أن تدخل الملف التحتي  &quot;fileadmin/&quot; كمسار.
مثلا لو كنت تريد أن تربط الملف بــ :  &quot;fileadmin/user_uploads/all/&quot;  إذاً أدخل  &quot;user_uploads/all&quot;
كمسار للربط

أما إذا كان المسار في الأساس معمول على مسار مُطلق فعيك أن تُدخل المسار المُطلق عيى السيرفر مثلاً &quot;/home/ftp_upload&quot; or &quot;C:/home/ftp_upload&quot;.


&lt;strong&gt;ملحوظة:&lt;/strong&gt;على أي الأحوال تأكد ان سيرفر الويب المُستخدم &lt;em&gt; على الأقل &lt;/em&gt; فيه الوضع read-access to the path. إذا لم يكن كذلك فإن الربط لمن يحدث بدون رسائل تحذيرية.
إذا كان لديك مشكلة في الربط جرب أولاً ربط بسيط باستخدام الربط النسبي في ال fileadmin . إذا لم يكن فيه مشكلة جرب بعدها إستخدام المسار المُطلق.

ربما تحتوي التعييرات للــ PHP على قيود عند إستخدامك في حالة الــ safe-mode لخاصية  features إذا كانت المُختــارة.
في هذه الحالة إستخدم المسار النسبي.</label>
			<label index="hidden.description">إستخدم هذه الخاصية لو كان رابط الملف</label>
			<label index="hidden.details">كل المستخدمين الذين يستعملون الربط سوف لا يستطيعون إستخدامه مرةً أخرى .هذا يحتوي على مستخدمين مسئولين .</label>
			<label index="base.description">إحسب أي من قيم المسار ممكن نعتبرها مسار مُطلق على السيرفر أو المسار النسبي إلى الملف إحسب أي من قيم المسار ممكن نعتبرها مسار مُطلق على السيرفر أو المسار النسبي إلى الملف  الفرعي fileadmin/</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="he" type="array">
			<label index=".description">מוצבי קבצים מתארים נתיב קבצים על השרת, יחסי או מוחלט.</label>
			<label index=".details">דרך יצירת רשומה של מוצב קבצים והנחת התייחסות אליו בקבוצת משתמשי ממשק אחורי, הנך יכול לאפשר גישת משתמשים למוצב קבצים במודול &quot;קובץ&gt;רשימה&quot;. עליך ליצור ולהגדיר לפחות מוצב קבצים אחד עם תיקייה &quot;_temp_&quot; בתוכו אם הנך רוצה לאפשר למשתמשים להעלות קבצים דרך דפדפן אינטרנט. מוצבי קבצים יכולים גם לעצב גישה לנתיב על השרת, אליו יש למשתמש גישת FTP. צריך לזכור רק להגדיר הרשאות קבצים על השרת בצורה נכונה, כך שמשתמש של השרת (שה-PHP משתמש בזהותו) נושא לפחות זכות קריאה לתיקיית FTP זו.</label>
			<label index="title.description">הכנס שם של מוצב קבצים.</label>
			<label index="path.description">הכנס נתיב של מוצב קבצים, יחסי או מוחלט, תלוי בהגדרתו של בסיס (BASE).</label>
			<label index="path.details">במיקרה בו הבסיס (BASE) מכוון להיות יחסי, הנתיב שמוצב נמצא בתת-תיקייה &quot;fileadmin/&quot; של האתר. לכן עליך לציין תת-תיקייה של &quot;fileadmin/&quot; בנתיב. לדוגמה, אם ברצונך ליצור מוצב ל-&quot;fileadmin/user_uploads/all/&quot; עליך לציין &quot;user_uploads/all&quot; בתור ערך לשדה &quot;נתיב&quot;. במידה ובסיס (BASE) הינו מוחלט - עליך לציין נתיב מוחלט על השרת, כגון &quot;/home/ftp_upload&quot; או &quot;C:/home/ftp_upload&quot;.
&lt;strong&gt;הערה:&lt;/strong&gt;
בכל מקרה, נא לוודע שמשתמש שבזהותו משתמש ה-PHP נושא לפחות זכות קריאה לנתיב. אם לא - המוצב פשוט לא יופיע, ללא כל אזהרה. אם יש בעיות , במיוחד עם מוצבים מוחלטים - נסה לצור מוצב פשוט יותר - כמו יחסי ל &quot;fileadmin&quot;. אם זה עובד כרצוי - נסה נתיב מוחלט.
תצורת PHP יכולה להטיל הגבלות נוספות. לכן כדאי יותר להשתמש בנתיבים יחסיים.</label>
			<label index="hidden.description">השתמש באפשרות זו כדי להפוך מוצב קבצים ללא זמין זמנית.</label>
			<label index="hidden.details">כל משתמשי ממשק האחורי לא יקבלו אישור גישה יותר. זה כולל משתמשי &quot;Admin&quot; גם.</label>
			<label index="base.description">קובע אם ערך של שדה &quot;נתיב&quot; הוא נתיב מוחלט או יחסי לתיקייה fileadmin.</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ua" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="lv" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="jp" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="vn" type="array">
		</languageKey>
	</data>
	<orig_hash type="array">
		<languageKey index="default" type="array">
			<label index=".description" type="integer">90189964</label>
			<label index=".details" type="integer">19507487</label>
			<label index="_.seeAlso" type="integer">220083613</label>
			<label index="title.description" type="integer">24921377</label>
			<label index="path.description" type="integer">40932089</label>
			<label index="path.details" type="integer">81389288</label>
			<label index="_path.seeAlso" type="integer">19760400</label>
			<label index="hidden.description" type="integer">191012042</label>
			<label index="hidden.details" type="integer">244149635</label>
			<label index="base.description" type="integer">89456305</label>
			<label index="_base.seeAlso" type="integer">236281219</label>
			<label index=".syntax" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_.image" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="title.details" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="title.syntax" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_title.seeAlso" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_title.image" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="path.syntax" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_path.image" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="hidden.syntax" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_hidden.seeAlso" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_hidden.image" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="base.details" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="base.syntax" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_base.image" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index=".alttitle" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index=".image_descr" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="title.alttitle" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="title.image_descr" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="path.alttitle" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="path.image_descr" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="hidden.alttitle" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="hidden.image_descr" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="base.alttitle" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="base.image_descr" type="integer">222419149</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="dk" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="de" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="no" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="it" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="fr" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="es" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="nl" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="cz" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="pl" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="si" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="fi" type="array">
			<label index=".description" type="integer">90189964</label>
			<label index=".details" type="integer">3417865</label>
			<label index="title.description" type="integer">24921377</label>
			<label index="path.description" type="integer">40932089</label>
			<label index="path.details" type="integer">223925609</label>
			<label index="hidden.description" type="integer">191012042</label>
			<label index="hidden.details" type="integer">244149635</label>
			<label index="base.description" type="integer">89456305</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="tr" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="se" type="array">
			<label index=".description" type="integer">90189964</label>
			<label index=".details" type="integer">3417865</label>
			<label index="title.description" type="integer">24921377</label>
			<label index="path.description" type="integer">40932089</label>
			<label index="path.details" type="integer">223925609</label>
			<label index="hidden.description" type="integer">191012042</label>
			<label index="hidden.details" type="integer">244149635</label>
			<label index="base.description" type="integer">89456305</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="pt" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ru" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ro" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ch" type="array">
			<label index=".description" type="integer">90189964</label>
			<label index=".details" type="integer">3417865</label>
			<label index="title.description" type="integer">24921377</label>
			<label index="path.description" type="integer">40932089</label>
			<label index="path.details" type="integer">223925609</label>
			<label index="hidden.description" type="integer">191012042</label>
			<label index="hidden.details" type="integer">244149635</label>
			<label index="base.description" type="integer">89456305</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="sk" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="lt" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="is" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="hr" type="array">
			<label index=".description" type="integer">90189964</label>
			<label index=".details" type="integer">3417865</label>
			<label index="_.seeAlso" type="integer">220083613</label>
			<label index="title.description" type="integer">24921377</label>
			<label index="path.description" type="integer">40932089</label>
			<label index="path.details" type="integer">223925609</label>
			<label index="_path.seeAlso" type="integer">19760400</label>
			<label index="hidden.description" type="integer">191012042</label>
			<label index="hidden.details" type="integer">244149635</label>
			<label index="base.description" type="integer">89456305</label>
			<label index="_base.seeAlso" type="integer">236281219</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="hu" type="array">
			<label index=".description" type="integer">90189964</label>
			<label index=".details" type="integer">3417865</label>
			<label index="title.description" type="integer">24921377</label>
			<label index="path.description" type="integer">40932089</label>
			<label index="path.details" type="integer">223925609</label>
			<label index="hidden.description" type="integer">191012042</label>
			<label index="hidden.details" type="integer">244149635</label>
			<label index="base.description" type="integer">89456305</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="gl" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="th" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="gr" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="hk" type="array">
			<label index=".description" type="integer">90189964</label>
			<label index=".details" type="integer">3417865</label>
			<label index="title.description" type="integer">24921377</label>
			<label index="path.description" type="integer">40932089</label>
			<label index="path.details" type="integer">223925609</label>
			<label index="hidden.description" type="integer">191012042</label>
			<label index="hidden.details" type="integer">244149635</label>
			<label index="base.description" type="integer">89456305</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="eu" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="bg" type="array">
			<label index=".description" type="integer">90189964</label>
			<label index="title.description" type="integer">24921377</label>
			<label index="path.description" type="integer">40932089</label>
			<label index="hidden.description" type="integer">191012042</label>
			<label index="hidden.details" type="integer">244149635</label>
			<label index="base.description" type="integer">89456305</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="br" type="array">
			<label index=".description" type="integer">90189964</label>
			<label index=".details" type="integer">3417865</label>
			<label index="title.description" type="integer">24921377</label>
			<label index="path.description" type="integer">40932089</label>
			<label index="path.details" type="integer">223925609</label>
			<label index="hidden.description" type="integer">191012042</label>
			<label index="hidden.details" type="integer">244149635</label>
			<label index="base.description" type="integer">89456305</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="et" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ar" type="array">
			<label index=".description" type="integer">90189964</label>
			<label index=".details" type="integer">3417865</label>
			<label index="title.description" type="integer">24921377</label>
			<label index="path.description" type="integer">40932089</label>
			<label index="path.details" type="integer">223925609</label>
			<label index="hidden.description" type="integer">191012042</label>
			<label index="hidden.details" type="integer">244149635</label>
			<label index="base.description" type="integer">89456305</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="he" type="array">
			<label index=".description" type="integer">90189964</label>
			<label index=".details" type="integer">3417865</label>
			<label index="title.description" type="integer">24921377</label>
			<label index="path.description" type="integer">40932089</label>
			<label index="path.details" type="integer">223925609</label>
			<label index="hidden.description" type="integer">191012042</label>
			<label index="hidden.details" type="integer">244149635</label>
			<label index="base.description" type="integer">89456305</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ua" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="lv" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="jp" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="vn" type="array">
		</languageKey>
	</orig_hash>
	<orig_text type="array">
		<languageKey index="default" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="dk" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="de" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="no" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="it" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="fr" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="es" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="nl" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="cz" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="pl" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="si" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="fi" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="tr" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="se" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="pt" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ru" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ro" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ch" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="sk" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="lt" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="is" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="hr" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="hu" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="gl" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="th" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="gr" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="hk" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="eu" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="bg" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="br" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="et" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ar" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="he" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ua" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="lv" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="jp" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="vn" type="array">
		</languageKey>
	</orig_text>
</T3locallang>