<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
	<meta type="array">
		<description>CSH for Extension Manager</description>
		<type>CSH</type>
		<fileId>EXT:lang/locallang_csh_em.php</fileId>
		<csh_table>_MOD_tools_em</csh_table>
		<labelContext type="array">
		</labelContext>
	</meta>
	<data type="array">
		<languageKey index="default" type="array">
			<label index="emconf_shy.alttitle">Shy</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.description">If set, the extension will normally be hidden in the EM because it might be a default extension or otherwise something which is not so important.</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.details">Use this flag if an extension is of ?rare interest? (which is not the same as un-important - just an extension not sought for very often...)
It does not affect whether or not it's enabled. Only display in EM.
Normally ?shy? is set for all extensions loaded by default according to TYPO3_CONF_VARS.</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.alttitle">Category</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.description">Which category the extension belongs to.</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.details">&lt;b&gt;be:&lt;/b&gt; Backend (Generally backend oriented, but not a module)

&lt;b&gt;module:&lt;/b&gt; Backend modules (When something is a module or connects with one)

&lt;b&gt;fe:&lt;/b&gt; Frontend (Generally frontend oriented, but not a ?true? plugin)

&lt;b&gt;plugin:&lt;/b&gt; Frontend plugins (Plugins inserted as a ?Insert Plugin? content element)

&lt;b&gt;misc:&lt;/b&gt; Miscellaneous stuff (Where not easily placed elsewhere)

&lt;b&gt;example:&lt;/b&gt; Example extension (Which serves as examples etc.)</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.alttitle">Dependencies of other extensions?</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.description">This is a list of other extension keys which this extension depends on being loaded BEFORE it self.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.details">The EM will manage that dependency while writing the extension list  to localconf.php</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.alttitle">Conflicts with other extensions?</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.description">List of extension keys of extensions with which this extension does not work (and so cannot be enabled before those other extensions are un-installed)</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.alttitle">Requested Loading priority</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.description">This tells the EM to try to put the extensions as the very first in the list. Default is last.</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.alttitle">Backend modules included</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.description">If any subfolders to an extension contains backend modules, those foldernames should be listed here.</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.details">It allows the EM to know about the existence of the module, which is important because the EM has to update the conf.php file of the module in order to set the correct TYPO3_MOD_PATH  constant.</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.alttitle">Development state</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.description">Which development state the extension is in.</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.details">&lt;b&gt;alpha&lt;/b&gt;
Very initial development. May do nothing at all.

&lt;b&gt;beta&lt;/b&gt;
Under current development. Should work partly but is not finished yet.

&lt;b&gt;stable&lt;/b&gt;
Stable and used in production.

&lt;b&gt;experimental&lt;/b&gt;
Nobody knows if this is going anywhere yet... Maybe still just an idea.

&lt;b&gt;test&lt;/b&gt;
Test extension, demonstrates concepts etc.</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.alttitle">Internally supported in core</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.description">This flag indicates that the core source code is specifically aware of the extension.</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.details">In order words this flag should convey the message that ?this extension could not be written without some core source code modifications?.

An extension is not internal just because it uses TYPO3 general classes eg. those from t3lib/.
True non-internal extensions are characterized by the fact that they could be written without making core source code changes, but relies only on existing classes  in TYPO3 and/or other extensions, plus its own scripts in the extension folder.</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.alttitle">Clear cache when installed</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.description">If set, the EM will request the cache to be cleared when this extension is installed.</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.alttitle">Existing tables modified</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.description">List of tablenames which are only modified - not fully created - by this extension.</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.details">Tables from this list found in the ext_tables.sql file of the extension</label>
			<label index=".alttitle">EM</label>
			<label index=".description">The Extension Manager (EM)</label>
			<label index=".details">TYPO3 can be extended in nearly any direction without loosing backwards compatibility. The Extension API provides a powerful framework for easily adding, removing, installing and developing such extensions to TYPO3. This is in particular powered by the Extension Manager (EM) inside TYPO3.

?Extensions? is a term in TYPO3 which covers two other terms, plugins and modules.

A plugin is something that plays a role on the website itself. Eg. a board, guestbook, shop etc. It is normally enclosed in a PHP class and invoked through a USER or USER_INT cObject from TypoScript. A plugin is an extension in the frontend.

A module is a backend application which has it's own position in the administration menu. It requires backend login and works inside the framework of the backend. We might also call something a module if it exploits any connectivity of an existing module, that is if it simply adds itself to the function menu of existing modules. A module is an extension in the backend.</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.alttitle">Private</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.description">If set, this version is not shown in the public list in the online repository.</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.details">&quot;Private&quot; uploads requires you to manually enter a special key (which will be shown to you after an upload has been completed) to be able to import and view details for the uploaded extension.
This is nice when you are working on something internally which you do not want others to look at.
You can set and clear the private flag every time you upload your extension.</label>
			<label index="_emconf_private.seeAlso">_MOD_tools_em:emconf_download_password</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.alttitle">Download password</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.description">Additional password required for download of private extensions.</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.details">Anybody who knows the &quot;special key&quot; assigned to the private upload will be able to import it. Specifying an import password allows you to give away the download key for private uploads and also require a password given in addition. The password can be changed later on.</label>
			<label index="_emconf_download_password.seeAlso">_MOD_tools_em:emconf_private</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.alttitle">Installation type</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.description">The type of the installation</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.details">The files for an extension are located in a folder named by the extension key. The location of this folder can be either inside typo3/sysext/,  typo3/ext/ or  typo3conf/ext/. The extension must be programmed so that it does automatically detect where it is located and can work from all three locations.

&lt;b&gt;Local location ?typo3conf/ext/?:&lt;/b&gt; This is where to put extensions which are local for a particular TYPO3 installation. The typo3conf/ dir is always local, containing local configuration (eg. localconf.php), local modules etc. If you put an extension here it will be available for this TYPO3 installation only. This is a ?per-database? way to install an extension.

&lt;b&gt;Global location ?typo3/ext/?:&lt;/b&gt; This is where to put extensions which are global for the TYPO3 source code on the web server. These extensions will be available for any TYPO3 installation sharing the source code.
When you upgrade your TYPO3 source code you probably want to copy the typo3/ext/ directory from the former source to the new source, overriding the default directory. In this way all global extension you use will be installed inside the new sourcecode. After that you can always enter TYPO3 and upgrade the versions if needed.
This is a ?per-server? way to install an extension.

&lt;b&gt;System location ?typo3/sysext/?:&lt;/b&gt; This is system default extensions which cannot and should not be updated by the EM.


&lt;b&gt;Loading precedence&lt;/b&gt;
Local extensions take precedence which means that if an extension exists both in typo3conf/ext/ and typo3/ext/ the one in typo3conf/ext/ is loaded. Likewise global extension takes predence over system extensions. This means that extensions are loaded in the order of priority local-global-system.
In effect you can therefore have - say - a ?stable? version of an extension installed in the global dir (typo3/ext/) which is used by all your projects on a server sharing source code, but on a single experimental project you can import the same extension in a newer ?experimental? version and for that particular project the locally available extension will be used instead.</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.alttitle">Installed twice or more?</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.description">Tells you if the extensions is installed in more than one of the System, Global or Local locations.</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.details">Because an extension can reside at three locations, System, Global and Local, this indicates if the extension is found in other locations than the current. In that case you should be aware which one of the extensions is loaded!</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.alttitle">Root files</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.description">List of the files in the extension folder. Does not list files in subfolders.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.alttitle">Database requirements</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.description">Shows you the requirements to the database tables and fields, if any.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.details">This will read from the files ext_tables.sql and ext_tables_static+adt.sql and show you which tables, fields and static tables are required with this extension.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.alttitle">Database requirements status</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.description">Displays the current status of the database compared to the extension requirements.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.details">If the extension is loaded which will display and error message if some tables or fields are not present in the database as they should be!</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.alttitle">Flags</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.description">A list of special codes which tells you something about what parts of TYPO3 the extension touches.</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.details">This is a list of the flags:

&lt;b&gt;Module:&lt;/b&gt; A true backend main/sub module is found to be added.

&lt;b&gt;Module+:&lt;/b&gt; The extension adds itself to the function menu of an existing backend module.

&lt;b&gt;loadTCA:&lt;/b&gt; The extension includes a function call to t3lib_div::loadTCA for loading a table. This potentially means that the system is slowed down, because the full table description of some table is always included. However there probably is a good reason for this to happen. Probably the extension tries to manipulate the TCA-config for an existing table in order to extend it.

&lt;b&gt;TCA:&lt;/b&gt; The extension contains configuration of a table in $TCA.

&lt;b&gt;Plugin:&lt;/b&gt; The extension adds a frontend plugin to the plugin list in Content Element type &quot;Insert Plugin&quot;.

&lt;b&gt;Plugin/ST43:&lt;/b&gt; TypoScript rendering code for the plugin is added to the static template &quot;Content (default)&quot;. &quot;Plugin&quot; and &quot;Plugin/ST43&quot; are commonly used together.

&lt;b&gt;Page-TSconfig:&lt;/b&gt; Default Page-TSconfig is added.

&lt;b&gt;User-TSconfig:&lt;/b&gt; Default User-TSconfig is added.

&lt;b&gt;TS/Setup:&lt;/b&gt; Default TypoScript Setup is added.

&lt;b&gt;TS/Constants:&lt;/b&gt; Default TypoScript Constants is added.</label>
			<label index="emconf_conf.description">Shows if the extension has a template for further lowlevel configuration.</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.alttitle">Static TypoScript files</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.description">Shows which TypoScript static files may be present</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.details">If the files ext_typoscript_constants.txt and/or ext_typoscript_setup.txt is found in the extension folder their are included in the hierarchy of all TypoScript templates in TYPO3 right after the inclusion of other static templates.</label>
			<label index="emconf_locallang.alttitle">locallang-files</label>
			<label index="emconf_locallang.description">Shows which files named &quot;locallang.php&quot; are present in the extension folder (recursive search). Such files are usually used to present an array $LOCAL_LANG with labels for the application in the system languages.</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.alttitle">Backend Module names</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.description">Shows which module names was found inside the extension.</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.alttitle">PHP Class names</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.description">Shows which PHP-classes were found in .php and .inc files.</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.alttitle">Errors</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.description">Displays if any serious errors with the extension was discovered.</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.alttitle">Namespace errors</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.description">Certain naming convensions apply to extensions. This displays any violations found.</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.details">The naming convensions are defined in the &quot;Inside TYPO3&quot; document. To make naming as simple as possible, try to avoid underscores in your extension keys.</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="dk" type="array">
			<label index="emconf_shy.alttitle">Sky</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="de" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="no" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="it" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="fr" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="es" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="nl" type="array">
			<label index="emconf_shy.alttitle">Verlegen</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.description">Als ingesteld zal deze extensie normaalgesproken verborgen zijn in de EM, omdat het een standaardextensie is of iets dat anders niet zo belangrijk is.</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.details">Gebruik deze vlag als een extensie van weinig belang is (niet hetzelfde als onbelangrijk - gewoon een extensie die niet vaak gebruikt wordt...)
Normaalgesproken staat &quot;verlegen&quot; ingesteld voor alle extensies die standaard geladen worden aan de hand van TYPO3_CONF_VARS.</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.alttitle">Categorie</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.description">Categorie van deze extensie</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.details">&lt;b&gt;be:&lt;/b&gt; Backend (Backendgeoriënteerd, maar geen module)

&lt;b&gt;module:&lt;/b&gt; Backend modules (Als iets een module is of van een module gebruik maakt)

&lt;b&gt;fe:&lt;/b&gt; Frontend (Algemeen frontend georiënteerd, maar geen &quot;echte&quot; plugin)

&lt;b&gt;plugin:&lt;/b&gt; Frontend plugins (Plugins ingevoegd als een &quot;Invoegen plugin&quot; inhoudselement)

&lt;b&gt;div:&lt;/b&gt; Diverse zaken (Die niet ergens anders ondergebracht kunnen worden)

&lt;b&gt;voorbeeld:&lt;/b&gt; Voorbeeld extensie (Dient als voorbeeld)</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.alttitle">Afhankelijk van andere extensies?</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.description">Dit is een lijst van andere extensie waar deze extensie van afhankelijk is. Deze dienen geladen te worden VOOR de extensie zelf.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.details">De EM regelt de afhankelijkheid terwijl de extensielijst naar de localconf geschreven wordt.</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.alttitle">Conflicteerd met andere extensies?</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.description">Lijst van extensiesleutels van extensies die niet met deze extensie werken (en dus niet geactiveerd kan worden voordat deze andere extensies gedeïnstalleerd zijn)</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.alttitle">Gewenste volgorde van laden</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.description">Dit zorgt ervoor dat de EM probeert de extensies als allereerste in de lijst zet. Standaard is laatste.</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.alttitle">Geïncludeerde backendmodules</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.description">Wanneer submappen van een extensie backendmodules bevatten dan dienen die mapnamen hier getoond te worden.</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.details">Dit zorgt ervoor dat de EM weet van het bestaan van de module. Dat is belangrijk, omdat de EM het conf.php bestand van de module moet actualiseren om de juiste TYPO3_MOD_PATH constante in te stellen.</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.alttitle">Ontwikkelingstoestand</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.description">In welke ontwikkelingstoestand de extensie zich bevindt.</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.details">&lt;b&gt;alfa&lt;/b&gt;
Beginstadium van ontwikkeling. Werkt misschien helemaal niet.V

&lt;b&gt;beta&lt;/b&gt;
In ontwikkeling. Moet gedeeltelijk werken, maar is nog niet af.

&lt;b&gt;stabiel&lt;/b&gt;
Stabiel en in productie.

&lt;b&gt;experimenteel&lt;/b&gt;
Niemand weet waar dit naar toe gaat... Misschien gewoon een idee.

&lt;b&gt;test&lt;/b&gt;
Test extensie voor concepten enz.</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.alttitle">Intern ondersteunt in de core</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.description">Deze vlag geeft aan dat de corecode zich specifiek bewust is van de aanwezigheid van de extensie.</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.details">Deze vlag dient de boodschap over te  brengen dat &quot;deze extensie niet geschreven kan worden zonder enige corebroncodemodificaties&quot;.

Een extensie is niet alleen intern omdat deze gebruik maakt van TYPO3's algemene classes zoals bijvoorbeeld die uit t3lib/. Daadwerkelijke niet-interne extensies worden gekarakteriseerd door het feit dat deze geschreven kunnen worden zonder gebruik te maken van corebroncodewijzigingen, maar alleen afhankelijk zijn van bestaande classes in TYPO3 en/of andere extensies plus eigen scripts in de extensiemap.</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.alttitle">Cache leegmaken wanneer geïnstalleerd</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.description">Wanneer dit ingesteld is dan zal de EM een verzoek doen de cache leeg te maken zodra de extensie geïnstalleerd is.</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.alttitle">Gewijzigde bestaande tabellen</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.description">Lijst van tabelnamen die alleen gewijzigd - niet aangemaakt - door deze extensie.</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.details">Tabellen van de lijst uit het ext_tables.sql bestand van deze extensie.</label>
			<label index=".alttitle">EM</label>
			<label index=".description">De extensie Manager (EM)</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.alttitle">Namen van backendmodules</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.alttitle">Fouten</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.alttitle">Namespace fouten</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="cz" type="array">
			<label index="emconf_shy.alttitle">Stydlivá</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.description">Pokud je nastaveno, bude rozšíření v EM běžně skryto, protože to může být základní rozšíření nebo něco jinak ne příliš důležitého.</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.details">Použijte tento příznak pokud je rozšíření &quot;nezajímavé&quot; (což není to samé jako nedůležité - jen je nikdo nehledá často ...)
Neovlivňuje, zda je nebo není zapnuté. Jen zobrazení v EM.
Běžně je příznak &quot;stydlivá&quot; nastaven pro všechna rozšíření, která se nahrávají podle TYPO3_CONF_VARS.</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="pl" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="si" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="fi" type="array">
			<label index="emconf_shy.alttitle">Piiloitteleva</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.description">Jos tämä on asetettu, on laajennsu normaalisti piiloitettu Laajennuksen Hallinnassa (EM) koska se voi olla oletuslaajennus tai muutoin sellainen joka ei olet ärkeä.</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.details">Käytä tät merkintää kun laajennus on &quot;vailla kiinnostusta&quot; (mikä ei suinkaan tarkoita merkityksetöntä - laajennus jota tarvitaan vain kovin harvoin...)
Ei vaikuta yleiseti toimintaa on ladattu vai ei. Näkyy ainoastaan Laajennusten Hallinnassa (EM).
Piiloitteleva (Shy) asetetaan yleensä laajennuksille jotka ladataan oletuksena TYPO3_CONF_VARS muuttujan mukaisesti.</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.alttitle">Luokka</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.description">Mihin luokkaan laajennus kuuluu.</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.details">&lt;b&gt;be:&lt;/b&gt; Tausta (yleensä taustaan liittyvä, muttei aliohjelma)

&lt;b&gt;module:&lt;/b&gt; Tausta aliohjelma (On jokin aliohjelma tai liittyy sellaiseen)

&lt;b&gt;fe:&lt;/b&gt; Etutoiminto (Yleisesti etutoimintaa liittyvä muttei suoranainen aliohjelma)

&lt;b&gt;plugin:&lt;/b&gt; Etutoiminto laajennus (Laajennus joka asennetaan kuten &quot;Lisää Laajennus&quot; (?Insert Plugin?) sisältö elementti)

&lt;b&gt;misc:&lt;/b&gt; Satunnainen (Laajennus jota ei voi määritellä muualle)

&lt;b&gt;example:&lt;/b&gt; Esimerkki laajennus (Laajennus joka on vain esimerkin luonteinen jne.)</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.alttitle">Riippuvuudet muihin laajennuksiin ?</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.description">Tämä on lista muiden laajennusten avaimista, jotka on ladattava ennenkuin tämä laajennus ladataan.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.details">Laajennusten Hallinta (EM) hoitaa riippuvuuden kirjoittaessaan laajennusten listan localconf.php tiedostoon.</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.alttitle">Konfliktit muiden laajennusten kanssa ?</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.description">Lista tämän laajennuksen kanssa toimimattomien laajennusten avaimista (ja joita ei voi asettaa ennekuin nuo laajennukset on poistettu asennuksesta)</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.alttitle">Haluttu lataamisen pririsointi</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.description">Tämän tarkoituksena on antaa Laajennusten Hallinnalle (EM) tieto laajennuksen asettamista ladattavaksi ensimmäisenä. Oletusarvo on lataus viimeisenä.</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.alttitle">Tausta-aliohjelmat jotka on lisätty</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.description">Jos laajennuksen mikä tahansa hakemisto sisältää tausta-aliohjelmia tulee ne (hakemistot) listata tähän.</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.details">Tämä mahdollistaa Laajennusten Hallinan (EM) tietävän aliohjelmista, joka on tarpeen jotta Laajennusten Hallinta voi päivittää conf.php tiedoston jotta voidaan asettaa oikea TYPO3_MOD_PATH vakio.</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.alttitle">Kehittämisen tila</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.description">Mihin kehittämitilaan laajennus kuuluu.</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.details">&lt;b&gt;alpha&lt;/b&gt;
Hyvin alkuvaihe. Voi olla ettei toimi lainkaan.

&lt;b&gt;beta&lt;/b&gt;
Kehittämisen alainen. Pitäisi toimia ainakin osittain muttei ole viimesitelty.

&lt;b&gt;stable&lt;/b&gt;
Vaka ja tuotantokelpoinen.

&lt;b&gt;experimental&lt;/b&gt;
Kukaan ei tiedä miten tulee käymään... Voi olla vain ajatuksen asteella.

&lt;b&gt;test&lt;/b&gt;
Testilaajennus, kuvastaa konseptia, ajatusta jne.</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.alttitle">Tuetaan sisäisesti ohjelmarungossa.</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.description">Tämä merkintä osoittaa että ohjelmarunko on tietoinen laajennuksesta.</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.details">Toisin sanoen, tämä merkintä ilmoittaa että &quot; tätä laajennnusta ei voi ilman jotain runko-ohjeman muutosta&quot;.

Laajennus ei ole sisäinen vain siksi että se käyttää jotain TYPO3n omialuokkia esim. luokkia t3lib/ hekemistosta.
Todellisia ei-sisäisiä laajennuksia luonnehtii se tosiasia että ne on voitu kirjoitaa ilman muutoksia runko-ohjelmistoon (core),vaan käyttävät vain jo olemassaolevia TYPO3n luokkia ja/tai muita laajennuksia, sekä omia scriptejä laajennuksen omassa hakemistossa.</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.alttitle">Tyhjää välimuisti (cache) kun laajennus asennetaan.</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.description">Jos asetettu, EM pyytää välimuistin tyhjennettäväksi kun tämä laajennus asennetaan.</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.alttitle">Olemassa olevia tauluja muotoiltu</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.description">Lista tauluista jotka ainoastaan muokataan - ei luoda - tällälaajennuksella.</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.details">Lista tauluista jotka ovat tämän laajennuksen ext_tables.sql tiedostossa.</label>
			<label index=".alttitle">Laajennuksen Hallinta (EM)</label>
			<label index=".description">Laajennuksen Hallinta (Extension Manager)</label>
			<label index=".details">TYPO3a voidaan laajentaa lähes miten tahansa menettämättä takaisin paluun mahdollisuutta. Laajennuksen käyttöliittymä (the Extension API) on tehokas perusta lisätä, poistaa, asentaa je kehittää helposti laajennuksiaTYPO3een. Tätä avustaa erityisesti tehokas Laajennuksen Hallinta (EM) TYPO3essa sisäisesti.

&quot;Laajennus&quot; on TYPO3n termi joka kattaa kasi termiä lisäyksen (plugin) ja aliohjelman (module).

Lisäys (plugin) on jotain jolla on rooli itse web-sivustolla. Esimerkikis. vieraskirja, kauppa jne. Se on normaalisti PHP luokkaja käynnistetään USER tai USER_INT cObjektina TypoScriptillä. Lisäys on laajennus edustatoimintoihin (www käyttäjälle näkyvä osa).

Aliohjelma on taustasovellus jolla on oma hallintavalikko taustatoiminnoissa. Se tarvitsee sisäänkirjoituksen taustatoimintoihin ja toimii taustatoimintojen sisällä. Voimme kutsua aliohjelmaksi myös mitä tahansa joka liittyy johonkin muuhun laajennukseen, joka yksinkertaisesti lisää toiminnan olemassa olevaan aliohjelmaan. Aliohjelma on laajennus taustatoimintoihin.</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.alttitle">Yksityinen</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.description">Jos asetettu, ei tätä versiota näytetä julkisesti online laajennusvarastosta.</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.details">&quot;Yksityinen&quot; lataus (upload) tarvitsee sinun käsin lisäävän erityisen avaimen (joka näytetään kun olet suorittanut latauksen onnistuneesti) voidaksesi ladata ja nähdä yksityiskohdat tästä ladatusta laajennnuksesta.
Tämä on tarkoituksen mukaista (ja käytännöllistä) kun haluat itseksesi työskennellä jonkin laajennuksen kanssa jota et halua näyttää muille.
Voit asettaa tai poistaa yksityisyys merkinnän joka kerta kun lataat laajennuksen.</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.alttitle">Imuroinnin (download) salasana</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.description">Yksityisen laajennuksen imurointiin tarvittava pakollinen salasana</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.details">Kuka tahansa tietää laajennuksesi &quot;erityis avaimen&quot; voi hakea sen. Antamalla lataus salasanan voit antaaimurointi oikeuden yksityisiin laajennuksiisi jotka vaativat myös salasanan. Salasanan voi vaihtaa myöhemmin.</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.alttitle">Asennuksen tyyppi</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.description">Asennuksen tyyppi</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.details">Laajennuksen tiedostot sijoitetaan laajennuksen avaimen mukaisesti nimettyyn  hakemistoon. Tämä hakemisto voi sijaita joko, typo3/sysext/, typo3/ext/ tai typo3conf/ext/ hakemistoissa. Laajennus on ohjelmoitava siten että se itse tietääsijaintinsaja voi toimia mistä tahansa kolmesta sijaintimahdollisuudesta käsin.

&lt;b&gt;Paikallinen sijainti ?typo3conf/ext/?:&lt;/b&gt; Tänne sijoitetaan laajennukset jotka ovat erityisiä tälle TYPO3 installaatiolle. Hakemisto typo3conf/ on aina paikallinen, sisältääpaikallisen konfiguroinnin (esim.localconf.php), paikalliset aliohjelmat jne. Jos sijoitat laajennuksen tänne on se käytettävissä vain tässä TYPO3 installaatiossa. Se on tietokantakohtainen.

&lt;b&gt;Globaali sijainti ?typo3/ext/?:&lt;/b&gt;  Tänne sijoitetään TYPO3 installaation globaalit laajennukset. Nämä laajennukset ovat käytettävissä kaikilleTYPO3 installaatiosssa.
Kun päivität TYPO3 lähde koodiasi haluat varmasti kopioida typo3/ext/ hakemiston alkuperäisestälähteestä uudeksi lähteeksi, kirjoittaen yli oleetushakemiston. Näin toimien kaikki käyttämäsi laajennukset asennetaan uuteen lähdekoodiin. Tämän jälkeen voit siirtyä TYPO3een ja päivittää ne versiot joita tarvitset.
Tämä on per-palvelin tapa installoida laajennus.

&lt;b&gt;System location ?typo3/sysext/?:&lt;/b&gt; Tämä on järjestelmän oletus laajennukset joita ei voi eikäsaa päivittää Laajennusten Hallinnalla (EM).

&lt;b&gt;Lataamisen järjestys&lt;/b&gt;
Paikalliset laajennukset ovat etuoikeutettuja eli jos laajennus on sekä  typo3conf/ext/ että typo3/ext/ hakemistoissa typo3conf/ext/ hakemistossa oleva ladataan. Samoin globaalit laajennukset ovat etuoikeutettuja järjestelmälaajennuksiin nähden. Tämä tarkoittaa että lataamisjärjestys on paikallinen-globaali-järjestelmä.
Toisin sanoen Sinulla voi olla - sanokaamme - &quot;vakaa&quot; versio laajennuksesta joka on installoitu  globaaliin hakemistoon jota kaikki hankkeet käyttävät ja jakavat yhteisen koodin,  mutta yksittäisessä hankeessa voi kokeilla samaa laajennusta &quot;kokeilu&quot; versiona ja jotain hanketta varten voit  käyttää paikallista versiota.</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.alttitle">Installoitu toistamiseen tai useammin ?</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.description">Kertoo Sinullejoslaajennus on asennettu useamman kerran joko Järjestelmä (System), Globaali (Global) tai Paikallinen (Local) hakemistoihin.</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.details">Koska laajennukset voidaan sijoittaa kolmeen eri paikkaan, System, Global tai Local,osoittaa tämä jos laajennus on muissakin kuin tämän hetkisessä. Tässä tapauksessa varmista mistä hakemistosta laajennus ladataan.</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.alttitle">Juuren tiedostot</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.description">Lista tiedostoissa laajennuksen hakemistossa.Ei sisällä tiedostoja alahakemistoista.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.alttitle">Tietokantavaatimukset</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.description">Näyttää vaatimukset tietokannan tauluihin ja tietoihin, jos mitään.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.details">Tämä lukee tiedostoista ext_tables.sql ja ext_tables_static+adt.sql näyttäen mitä tauluja, tietoja sekä staattisia tauluja tarvitaan tässä laajennuksessa.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.alttitle">Tietokantavaatimusten tila</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.description">Näyttää tietokannantilan verrattuna laajennuksen vaatimuksiin.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.details">Näyttää virheilmoituksen jos laajennus on ladattu eikä tietokannan taulut tai tiedot vastaa sitä miten niiden tulisi olla.</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.alttitle">Merkinnät</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.description">Lista erityisistä koodeista jotka kertovat mitä TYPO3n osia laajennus koskee.</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.details">Tämä on lista merkinnöistä:

&lt;b&gt;Module:&lt;/b&gt; Todellinen tausta ohjelma/aliohjelmajoka onlöydetty lisättäväksi.

&lt;b&gt;Module+:&lt;/b&gt; Laajennus lisää itsensä jo olemassa olevan tausta aliohjelman valikkoon.

&lt;b&gt;loadTCA:&lt;/b&gt; Laajennus sisältää toiminta kutsun t3lib_div::loadTCA taulun lataamiseksi. Tämä mahdollisesti tarkoittaa järjestelmän hidastumista, koska täydellinen kuvaus joistakin tauluista on aina muistissa. Voi olla ettätähän on hyväkin syy. Voi olla että laajennus yrittää manipuloida TCA-config tietoja laajentaakseen olemassa olevaa taulua.

&lt;b&gt;TCA:&lt;/b&gt; Laajennus sisältää taulun konfiguraation $TCAssa.

&lt;b&gt;Plugin:&lt;/b&gt; Laajennus lisää edustatoimintojen lisäyksen lisäytten listalle Sisältö Elementtien tyypiksi &quot;Lisää plugin&quot;.

&lt;b&gt;Plugin/ST43:&lt;/b&gt; TypoScript toiminta koodi lisäykselle on lisätty stattiseen mallinteeseen&quot;Sisältö (oletus)&quot; (&quot;Content (default)&quot;). &quot;Plugin&quot; ja &quot;Plugin/ST43&quot; käytetään yleisesti yhdessä.

&lt;b&gt;Page-TSconfig:&lt;/b&gt; Oletus Page-TSconfig on lisätty.

&lt;b&gt;User-TSconfig:&lt;/b&gt; Oletus User-TSconfig on lisätty.

&lt;b&gt;TS/Setup:&lt;/b&gt; Oletus TypoScript Asetukset (Setup) on lisätty.

&lt;b&gt;TS/Constants:&lt;/b&gt; Oletus TypoScript Vakiot on lisätty.</label>
			<label index="emconf_conf.description">Näyttää jos laajennuksella on mallinne (template) alemman tason konfigurointia varten.</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.alttitle">Staattiset TypoScript tiedostot</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.description">Näyttää mitkä staattiset TypoScript tiedostot voivat olla voimassa</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.details">Jos tiedostot ext_typoscript_constants.txt ja/tai ext_typoscript_setup.txt löytyvät laajennuksen hakemistosta ne lisätään kaikkiiTypoScript mallinteisiin heti muiden staatisten mallinteiden jälkeen.</label>
			<label index="emconf_locallang.alttitle">locallang-tiedostot</label>
			<label index="emconf_locallang.description">Näyttää mitä &quot;locallang.php&quot; tiedostoja löytyy laajennuksen hakemistoista (rekursiivinen haku). Nämä tiedostot ovat yleensä $LOCAL_LANG taulokoita joissa on tekstit sovelluksen kullekin järjestelmän kielelle.</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.alttitle">Tausta aliohjelmien nimet</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.description">Näyttää mitkä aliohjelmien nimet löytyvät laajennuksesta.</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.alttitle">PHP Luokka nimet</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.description">Näyttää mitkä PHP-luokat löytyvät .phpja .inc tiedostoista.</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.alttitle">Virheet</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.description">Tämä näyttää jos laajennuksesta löytyy vakavia virheitä.</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.alttitle">Namespace virheitä</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.description">Laajennusten nimeämiseen on olemassa käytäntö. Tämä näyttää mitä virheitä löytyy.</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.details">Nimeämiskäytäntö on selvitetty &quot;Inside TYPO3&quot; dokumentissa. Nimien pitämiseksi mahdollisimman yksinkertaisina, pyri välttämään alaviivan käyttöä laajennustesi nimissä.</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="tr" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="se" type="array">
			<label index="emconf_shy.alttitle">Blyg</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.description">När detta är valt, kommer extensionen att gömmas i EM eftersom den kanske är en standardextension eller något, som inte är så viktigt.</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.details">Använd denna &quot;flagga&quot; om en extension är mindre intressant (vilket inte betyder att den skulle vara ointressan - men en som inte söks så ofta...)
Det har ingen betydelse om extensionen är tillåten eller inte. Visas endast i EM. Normalt ger man värdet &quot;Blyg&quot; åt alla de extensions, som laddas som standard enligt TYPO3_CONF_VARS.</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.alttitle">Kategori</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.description">Berättar vilken kategori extensionen hör till.</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.details">&lt;b&gt;be:&lt;/b&gt; Backend (I regel för backend, men inte en modul)

&lt;b&gt;module:&lt;/b&gt; Backend moduler (Om någonting är en modul eller hör till en sådan)

&lt;b&gt;fe:&lt;/b&gt; Frontend (I regel för frontend, men inte en riktig plugin)

&lt;b&gt;plugin:&lt;/b&gt; Frontend plugin (Plugins som kan infogas som ett &quot;Infoga plugin&quot;-innehållselement)

&lt;b&gt;misc:&lt;/b&gt; Material av olika art (Sådant som är svårt att placera någon annanstans)

&lt;b&gt;example:&lt;/b&gt; Exempel på extensions (Fungeras om exempel osv.)</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.alttitle">Beroende av andra extensions?</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.description">Detta är en lista på andra extension-nycklar som denhär extensionen är beroende av att laddas FÖRE sig själv.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.details">EM kan sköta om beroendet genom att skriva extension-listan till localconf.php</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.alttitle">Konflikt med en annan extension?</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.description">En lista över extension-nycklar med vilka denna extension inte fungerar (och kan alltså inte startas före den andra extensionen är avinstallerad)</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.alttitle">Begärd laddningsprioritet</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.description">Berättar för EM att försöka lägga denna extension som den allra första i listan. Standard är att den läggs till i slutet.</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.alttitle">Backend-moduler inkluderade</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.description">Om någon extensions underkatalog innehåller en backend-modul, skall deras katalognamn listas här.</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.details">Ger EM en möjlighet att veta om en modul,  som är viktig därför att EM måste uppdatera modulens conf.php-fil för att rätt konstant TYPO3_MOD_PATH skall ställas in.</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.alttitle">Utvecklingsskede</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.description">Berättar vilket utvecklingsskede extensionen är i.</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.details">&lt;b&gt;alpha&lt;/b&gt;
Utvecklingen på mycket tidigt stadie. Kanske inte gör något alls.

&lt;b&gt;beta&lt;/b&gt;
Utveckling på gång. Fungerar delvis men arbetet fortsätter.

&lt;b&gt;stable&lt;/b&gt;
Stabil och i produktivt bruk.

&lt;b&gt;experimental&lt;/b&gt;
Ingen vet om dethär skall bli något.. Kanske bara en idé.

&lt;b&gt;test&lt;/b&gt;
Test-extension, demonstrerar olika sätt mm.</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.alttitle">Full internatinell support</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.description">Denna märkning betyder att kärnkällkoden är uppmärksam på extensionen.</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.details">Med andra ord betyder denna märkning, att &quot;denna extension kunde inte skrivas utan att några ändringar i kärnkällkoden gjordes&quot;.

En extension är inte intern bara därför att den använder TYPO3:s allmänna klasser, dvs från t3lib/.
Äkta icke-interna extensioner karaktäriseras av det faktum att de kan skrivas utan att göra ändringar i kärnkällkoden, men de är endast relaterade till existerande klasser i TYPO3 och/eller andra extensioner, plus deras egna skript i extensionsfoldern.</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.alttitle">Töm mellanminnet efter installationen</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.description">Om detta är valt, kommer EM att begära att mellanminnet töms då extensionen är installerad.</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.alttitle">Existerande tabeller ändrade</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.description">En lista på de tabeller, som endast ändrats - inte skapats - av denna extension.</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.details">Tabeller från denna lista finns i ext_tables.sql-filen i extensionen</label>
			<label index=".alttitle">EM</label>
			<label index=".description">Extension-managern (EM)</label>
			<label index=".details">TYPO3 can be extended in nearly any direction without loosing backwards compatibility. The Extension API provides a powerful framework for easily adding, removing, installing and developing such extensions to TYPO3. This is in particular powered by the Extension Manager (EM) inside TYPO3.

?Extensions? is a term in TYPO3 which covers two other terms, plugins and modules.

A plugin is something that plays a role on the website itself. Eg. a board, guestbook, shop etc. It is normally enclosed in a PHP class and invoked through a USER or USER_INT cObject from TypoScript. A plugin is an extension in the frontend.

A module is a backend application which has it's own position in the administration menu. It requires backend login and works inside the framework of the backend. We might also call something a module if it exploits any connectivity of an existing module, that is if it simply adds itself to the function menu of existing modules. A module is an extension in the backend.</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.alttitle">Privat</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.description">Om förkryssad kommer denna version inte att synas i den offentliga listan.</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.details">&quot;Private&quot; uploads requires you to manually enter a special key (which will be shown to you after an upload has been completed) to be able to import and view details for the uploaded extension.
This is nice when you are working on something internally which you do not want others to look at.
You can set and clear the private flag every time you upload your extension.</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.alttitle">Lösenord för nerladdning</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.description">Ett extra lösenord som behövs för att ladda ner privata extensioner.</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.details">Anybody who knows the &quot;special key&quot; assigned to the private upload will be able to import it. Specifying an import password allows you to give away the download key for private uploads and also require a password given in addition. The password can be changed later on.</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.alttitle">Installationstyp</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.description">Typ av installation</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.details">The files for an extension are located in a folder named by the extension key. The location of this folder can be either inside typo3/sysext/, typo3/ext/ or typo3conf/ext/. The extension must be programmed so that it does automatically detect where it is located and can work from all three locations.

&lt;b&gt;Local location ?typo3conf/ext/?:&lt;/b&gt; This is where to put extensions which are local for a particular TYPO3 installation. The typo3conf/ dir is always local, containing local configuration (eg. localconf.php), local modules etc. If you put an extension here it will be available for this TYPO3 installation only. This is a ?per-database? way to install an extension.

&lt;b&gt;Global location ?typo3/ext/?:&lt;/b&gt; This is where to put extensions which are global for the TYPO3 source code on the web server. These extensions will be available for any TYPO3 installation sharing the source code.
When you upgrade your TYPO3 source code you probably want to copy the typo3/ext/ directory from the former source to the new source, overriding the default directory. In this way all global extension you use will be installed inside the new sourcecode. After that you can always enter TYPO3 and upgrade the versions if needed.
This is a ?per-server? way to install an extension.

&lt;b&gt;System location ?typo3/sysext/?:&lt;/b&gt; This is system default extensions which cannot and should not be updated by the EM.


&lt;b&gt;Loading precedence&lt;/b&gt;
Local extensions take precedence which means that if an extension exists both in typo3conf/ext/ and typo3/ext/ the one in typo3conf/ext/ is loaded. Likewise global extension takes predence over system extensions. This means that extensions are loaded in the order of priority local-global-system.
In effect you can therefore have - say - a ?stable? version of an extension installed in the global dir (typo3/ext/) which is used by all your projects on a server sharing source code, but on a single experimental project you can import the same extension in a newer ?experimental? version and for that particular project the locally available extension will be used instead.</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.alttitle">Installerad dubbelt eller ännu flere gåner?</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.description">Berättar om extensionen är installerad i flere än ett system, globalt eller lokalt ställe.</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.details">Because an extension can reside at three locations, System, Global and Local, this indicates if the extension is found in other locations than the current. In that case you should be aware which one of the extensions is loaded!</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.alttitle">Rotfiler</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.description">Listar filerna i extensionens katalog. Visar inte filer i underkataloger.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.alttitle">Databasens krav</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.description">Visar vilka krav databasens tabeller och fält ställer, om några.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.details">This will read from the files ext_tables.sql and ext_tables_static+adt.sql and show you which tables, fields and static tables are required with this extension.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.alttitle">Statusen av databasens krav</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.description">Visar nuvarande ställningen i databasen jämförd med extensionens krav.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.details">If the extension is loaded which will display and error message if some tables or fields are not present in the database as they should be!</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.alttitle">Flaggor</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.description">En lista på specialkoder som berättar någonting om vilka delar av TYPO3 som extensionen berör.</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.details">This is a list of the flags:

&lt;b&gt;Module:&lt;/b&gt; A true backend main/sub module is found to be added.

&lt;b&gt;Module+:&lt;/b&gt; The extension adds itself to the function menu of an existing backend module.

&lt;b&gt;loadTCA:&lt;/b&gt; The extension includes a function call to t3lib_div::loadTCA for loading a table. This potentially means that the system is slowed down, because the full table description of some table is always included. However there probably is a good reason for this to happen. Probably the extension tries to manipulate the TCA-config for an existing table in order to extend it.

&lt;b&gt;TCA:&lt;/b&gt; The extension contains configuration of a table in $TCA.

&lt;b&gt;Plugin:&lt;/b&gt; The extension adds a frontend plugin to the plugin list in Content Element type &quot;Insert Plugin&quot;.

&lt;b&gt;Plugin/ST43:&lt;/b&gt; TypoScript rendering code for the plugin is added to the static template &quot;Content (default)&quot;. &quot;Plugin&quot; and &quot;Plugin/ST43&quot; are commonly used together.

&lt;b&gt;Page-TSconfig:&lt;/b&gt; Default Page-TSconfig is added.

&lt;b&gt;User-TSconfig:&lt;/b&gt; Default User-TSconfig is added.

&lt;b&gt;TS/Setup:&lt;/b&gt; Default TypoScript Setup is added.

&lt;b&gt;TS/Constants:&lt;/b&gt; Default TypoScript Constants is added.</label>
			<label index="emconf_conf.description">Visar om extensionen har en template för framtida lågnivåkonfigurering.</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.alttitle">Statiska TypoScript filer</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.description">Visar vilka statiska TypoScript-filer kan förekomma</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.details">If the files ext_typoscript_constants.txt and/or ext_typoscript_setup.txt is found in the extension folder their are included in the hierarchy of all TypoScript templates in TYPO3 right after the inclusion of other static templates.</label>
			<label index="emconf_locallang.alttitle">locallang-filer</label>
			<label index="emconf_locallang.description">Shows which files named &quot;locallang.php&quot; are present in the extension folder (recursive search). Such files are usually used to present an array $LOCAL_LANG with labels for the application in the system languages.</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.alttitle">Backend-modulernas namn</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.description">Visar vilka modulnamn som hittades i extensionen</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.alttitle">PHP klassnamn</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.description">Visar vilka PHP-klasser som hittades i .php och .inc filerna.</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.alttitle">Fel</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.description">Visar allvarliga fel i extensionen.</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.alttitle">Fel i namnen</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.description">Vissa benämningsregler finns för extensionerna. Här visas eventuella fel i namnen.</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.details">The naming convensions are defined in the &quot;Inside TYPO3&quot; document. To make naming as simple as possible, try to avoid underscores in your extension keys.</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="pt" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ru" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ro" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ch" type="array">
			<label index="emconf_shy.alttitle">Shy</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.description">如果设置,扩展通常是在EM中被隐藏,因为它也许是一个默认的扩展或者是一些不重要的东西.</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.details">如果扩展是“少有兴趣“(它不等同于不重要 - 只是扩展不经常被搜寻...)则使用此标记
并不影响它是否可用.只是在EM中显示.
通常根据TYPO3_CONF_VARS为所有缺省情况下装载的扩展设置“shy“.</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.alttitle">种类</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.description">扩展属于什么种类.</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.details">&lt;b&gt;后端:&lt;/b&gt; 后端 (通常面向后端,但不是一个模块)

&lt;b&gt;模块:&lt;/b&gt; 后端模块 (如果是一个模块和与一块连接)

&lt;b&gt;前端:&lt;/b&gt; 前端 (通常面向前端,但不是一个 “真”插件)

&lt;b&gt;插件:&lt;/b&gt; 前端插件(插件作为一个“插入插件”内容元素被插入 )

&lt;b&gt;杂项:&lt;/b&gt; 杂项元素 (不能轻易被放在其它什么地方)

&lt;b&gt;举例:&lt;/b&gt; 举例扩展 (作为例子等)</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.alttitle">依附于其他扩展?</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.description">这是一个其他扩展键的列表,这个扩展在取决于在它本身之前被装载.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.details">在将扩展列表写入localconf.php时EM将管理从属关系</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.alttitle">与其它扩展冲突?</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.description">带有此扩展的扩展的扩展键不工作(并且在其它扩展卸载前不能成为可用)</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.alttitle">请求的装载优先权</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.description">这告诉EM试着把扩展放到列表的最前.缺省情况下是在最后.</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.alttitle">包含后端模块</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.description">如果至扩展的任何子目录包含后端模块,那些文件夹名称应在此被列出.</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.details">这允许EM获知模块的存在,这很重要.因为EM必须更新模块的conf.php文件来设置正确的TYPO3-MOD_PATH常数.</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.alttitle">开发状态</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.description">扩展在哪个开发状态下.</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.details">&lt;b&gt;alpha&lt;/b&gt;
最初的开发.根本无需做什么.

&lt;b&gt;beta&lt;/b&gt;
正在开发. 部分可以工作但还未完成.

&lt;b&gt;稳定的&lt;/b&gt;
稳定的并且使用在产品中.

&lt;b&gt;实验&lt;/b&gt;
没有人指导将会怎样...可能只是一个想法.

&lt;b&gt;测试&lt;/b&gt;
测试扩展,证明概念等.</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.alttitle">核心中内部支持</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.description">此标记标示出扩展的中心源代码.</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.details">另外说来此标记应该传达此信息“此扩展没有一些核心源代码的修改不
能被写出来”.
一扩展不是内部的就因为它使用了从t3lib/来的TYPO3普通类.
真正不在内部的扩展表现了如此特点它能不更改源代码被书写, 但仅
仅依赖于TYPO3中的类和/或其它扩展, 加上它自己在扩展文件夹中的
原本.</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.alttitle">当安装时清除存储</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.description">如果设置,扩展管理器将需要清除存储器当扩展安装时.</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.alttitle">现有的表格修改</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.description">表格命名列表它仅仅被修改而非被完全创建-在此扩展中</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.details">此列表的表格建立在ext_tables.sql文件的扩展中</label>
			<label index=".alttitle">扩展管理器</label>
			<label index=".description">扩展管理器(EM)</label>
			<label index=".details">TYPO3能在几乎任何方向而不需不稳定的向后的兼容性下被扩展.扩展
API对简单地添加, 消除和开发这样的扩展到TYPO3中提供一个强大的
框架. 这是通过扩展管理器在TYPO3内特别的推动力.
&quot;扩展&quot;是TYPO3的条目它包含两个其它的条目, 插件和模块.
插件是在网页上执行它的任务的一件东西. 例如一个底板, 客户本, 商店
等. 它通常情况附属于一个PHP类并且and 通过一个USER或USER_INT
cObject 从TypoScript中调用. 一个插件是在前端中的一个扩展.
一个模块是一个后端应用程序它有它自己在管理器菜单中的位置的. 它
需要后端登陆并且在后端框架中工作.我们可能也叫一些东西模块如果
它开发任何存在模块的连通性, 那就是如果它简单地添加它自己到存在
模块的功能菜单. 一个模块是在后端中的一个扩展.</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.alttitle">私人的</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.description">如果设置,此版本没有在在线存储器公共列表中显示.</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.details">&quot;私人&quot;上传需要您手动输入一个特别钥匙(当一个上传完成后它将为您
显示)才能输入和观看上传扩展的细节.
当您在内部工作的时候您不想使其他人看到您的工作这是非常好的.
您能在任何时间设置并清除私人标记当您上传您的扩展时.</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.alttitle">下载密码</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.description">私人扩展下载需要另外的密码.</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.details">任何明白&quot;特别钥匙&quot;分配的私人上传的人将能够输入它.在指定输入密码 allows you to give away the download key for private uploads and also require a password given in addition.            此密码能在不久被改变.The password can be changed later on.</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.alttitle">安装类型</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.description">安装的类型</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.details">此对扩展的文件是定位在一个由扩展钥匙命名的文件夹中. 文件夹中的
定位可任意在typo3/sysext/, typo3/ext/或 typo3conf/ext/中. 扩展必
须被规划以至它能自动发觉定位位置并且能在所有3个定位的位置工作.
&lt;b&gt;局部定位“typo3conf/ext/”:&lt;/b&gt; 这是把扩展放置到那里，它对
TYPO3特别安装是局部的.typo3conf/ dir总是局 部的,包含局部配置(例
如localconf.php), 局部模块等. 如果您在此放置一个扩展它仅仅对此
TYPO3安装有用.这是一个&quot;单一-数据库&quot;方法来安装一个扩展.
&lt;b&gt;全局定位“typo3/ext/”:&lt;/b&gt;这是把扩展放置到那里，它对TYPO3
网页服务器上源代码全局的. 此┱苟运??TYPO3安装分享代胧怯杏?
的.当您升级您的TYPO3源代码也许您想复制typo3/ext/目录从以前的
源代码到新的源. 在此以后您能够总是输入TYPO3并按需要升级版本.
这是一个“单一-服务器” 方法来安装一个扩展.
&lt;b&gt;系统定位 “typo3/sysext/”:&lt;/b&gt;这是系统默认的扩展它不能并
不应该被扩展管理器更正.
&lt;b&gt;优先安装&lt;/b&gt;
局部扩展拥有热?且馕蹲湃绻?桓隼┱勾嬖谟趖ypo3conf/ext/和
typo3/ext/两者中那么安装那个在typo3conf/ext/里的那个扩展. 同样全
局扩展比系统扩展拥有优先全. 这意味着扩展在局部-全局-系统中被优先
安装. 结果您因此能有-比方说- 一个&quot;稳定&quot; 的安装在全局显示文件列表
里的一个扩展版本(typo3/ext/) 它是在您服务器上所有的项目中被使用
的源代码, 但在单一实验项目您能输入相同的扩展在新的&quot;实验&quot; 版本下
并且对那个详细的项目局部地有效扩展将被来代替使用.</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.alttitle">两次安装或更多?</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.description">告诉您是否扩展安装在多个系统中,整体的或局部的位置.</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.details">因为一个扩展能位于三个位置,系统,全局和局部, 它表明是否扩展相比当前在其它位置被建立. 在此情况下您应该</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.alttitle">根文件</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.description">文件列表扩展文件夹.没有列出子目录的文件.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.alttitle">数据库要求</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.description">给您展示数据库表格和文件的要求,如果任何.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.details">这将从ext_tables.sql和ext_tables_static+adt.sql文件中读取并且给您展示那个表格, 文件和静态表格</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.alttitle">数据库需求状况</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.description">显示数据库当前状态对扩展需求进行比较.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.details">如果扩展被加载且如果一些表格或域不出现它们应该位于的数据库中扩展将被显示并且是错误信息!</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.alttitle">标记</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.description">特别代码的一个列表它告诉您TYPO3的一些扩展涉及点.</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.details">这是一个标记的列表:
&lt;b&gt;模块:&lt;/b&gt;一个真正的主/从模块被建立并被添加.
&lt;b&gt;模块+:&lt;/b&gt;此扩展添加它自己到一个存在的后端模块的功能菜单中.
&lt;b&gt;安装TCA:&lt;/b&gt;此扩展包括一个功能叫做t3lib_div::loadTCA为安
装表格作用的. 这潜在的意味着 系统慢下来了, 因为一些表格的完全描
述总是包括的. 无论如何它也许是对此所发生的一个好的理由. 扩展也许
尝试去扩充现有的表格来操作TCA-配置.
&lt;b&gt;TCA:&lt;/b&gt;此扩展包含在$TCA里的一个表格的配置.
&lt;b&gt;插件:&lt;/b&gt;此扩展添加一个前移的插件到内容元素类型&quot;嵌入擦件&quot;
的插件列表中.
&lt;b&gt;插件/ST43:&lt;/b&gt; TypoScript插件的翻译代码被添加到静态模板&quot;
内容(默认)&quot;中. &quot;插件&quot;和 &quot;插件/ST43
&quot;通常被一起使用.
&lt;b&gt;页面-TSconfig:&lt;/b&gt;默认页面-TSconfig已添加.
&lt;b&gt;用户-TSconfig:&lt;/b&gt;默认用户-TSconfig已添加.
&lt;b&gt;TS/设置:&lt;/b&gt;默认TypoScript设置已添加.
&lt;b&gt;TS/常量:&lt;/b&gt;默认TypoScript常量已添加.</label>
			<label index="emconf_conf.description">显示是否此扩展有一个对更多低水准的配置附和的模板</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.alttitle">静态TypoScript文件</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.description">显示哪个TypoScript静态文件可以呈现</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.details">如果文件ext_typoscript_constants.txt和/或ext_typoscript_setup.txt 在扩展文件夹中已建立,它们是在包含其它静态模板后包含在TYPO3里所有TypoScript模板的层次上.</label>
			<label index="emconf_locallang.alttitle">locallang文件</label>
			<label index="emconf_locallang.description">显示哪些以&quot;locallang.php&quot; 命名的文件显示在扩展文件夹中(返回查寻).此类文件通常以系统语言为应用程序显示一个带标签的数组$LOCAL_LANG.</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.alttitle">后端模块名称</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.description">显示哪些模块名称在扩展中被发现.</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.alttitle">PHP类名称</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.description">显示哪些PHP-类在.php和.inc文件中被发现.</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.alttitle">错误</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.description">显示是否发现了任何扩展的严重错误.</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.alttitle">名称空间错误</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.description">某些命名协定应用于扩展. 这显示任何发现了的非法命名.</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.details">命名协定在&quot;Inside TYPO3&quot; 文档中定义.为了使命名尽可能的简单,试着在您的扩展键中避免下划线.</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="sk" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="lt" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="is" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="hr" type="array">
			<label index="emconf_shy.alttitle">Prikriveno</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.description">Ako je postavljeno, ekstenzija će u biti skrivena u EM-u, npr. jer se radi o uobičajenoj ekstenziji ili nije od veće važnosti.</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.details">Koristite ovu zastavicu ako je mali interes za ekstenziju (to ne znači
da nije važna vć smo da nije često tražena...)
Ne utječe na uključenost ekstenzije, samo na prikaz u EM-u.
Uobičajeno je opcija 'skriveno' postavljena za sve ekstenzije koje
su standardno učitane u skladu s TYPO3_CONF_VARS.</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.alttitle">Kategorija</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.description">Kojoj kategoriji pripada ekstenzija</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.details">&lt;b&gt;be:&lt;/b&gt; Backend (Uobičajeno backend orijentirana,
ali nije modul)

&lt;b&gt;modul:&lt;/b&gt; Backend moduli (Kada je nešto modul
ili se spaja sa modulom)

&lt;b&gt;fe:&lt;/b&gt; Frontend (Uobičajeno frontend orijentirana,
ali nije &quot;pravi&quot; plugin)

&lt;b&gt;plugin:&lt;/b&gt; Frontend plugin-ovi (Plugin-ovi ubačeni kao
sadržajni elementi &quot;Ubaci Plugin&quot; metode)

&lt;b&gt;razno:&lt;/b&gt; Razne stvari (Kada se ne mogu drugdje smejstiti)

&lt;b&gt;primjer:&lt;/b&gt; Primjer ekstenzija (Koja služi kao primjer, itd.)</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.alttitle">Ovisnost o drugim ekstenzijama?</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.description">Ovo je lista ključeva ostalih ekstenzija o kojima ova ekstenzija ovisi i koje moraju biti učitane PRIJE nje same.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.details">EM će obraditi tu ovisnost dok bude pisao popis ekstenzija u localconf.php.</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.alttitle">Konflikti s drugim ekstenzijama?</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.description">Popis ključeva onih ekstenzija s kojim dotična ekstenzija dolazi u sukob (i zato nemože biti uključena prije nego su ostale isključene).</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.alttitle">Traženi prioritet učitavanja</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.description">Ovo govori EM-u da pokuša upisati ekstenzije na vrh liste. Standardno je na kraj liste.</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.alttitle">Uključi backend module</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.description">Ako neki poddirektoriji ekstenzije sadrže backend module, imena tih direktorija moraju ovdje biti popisana.</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.details">Omogućava EM-u informacije o postojanju modula, što je bitno jer EM mora osvježiti datoteku modula conf.php kako bi se valjano postavila TYPO3_MOD_PATH konstanta.</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.alttitle">Status razvoja</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.description">U kojem se statusu razvoja nalazi ekstenzija.</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.details">&lt;b&gt;alfa&lt;/b&gt;
Početni razvoj. Ne mora biti funkcionalna.

&lt;b&gt;beta&lt;/b&gt;
Trenutno u razvoju. Djelomično funkcionalna, ali nije završena.

&lt;b&gt;stabilna&lt;/b&gt;
Stabilna, koristi se u produkciji.

&lt;b&gt;experimentalna&lt;/b&gt;
Nepoznanica je da li će uopće biti stvarnih rezultata.
Možda se radi samo o ideji.

&lt;b&gt;test&lt;/b&gt;
Test ekstenzije, predstavljanje koncepata, itd.</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.alttitle">Interno podržan u jezgri sustava.</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.description">Ova zastavica ukazuje da ekstenzija posebno utječe na izvorni kod jezgre sustava.</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.details">U stvari ova zastavica bi trebala upozoravati na činjenicu da
&quot;ekstenzija nije mogla biti napisana bez izmjena u izvornom kodu sustava&quot;

Ekstenzija nije interna samo zato jer upotrebljava TYPO3 opće klase,
npr. one iz t3lib/.
Prave ne-interne ekstenzije obilježava činjenica da su napisane
bez uvođenja promjena u izvornom kodu jezgre sustava. One se
uz svoje skripte u pretincu ekstenzije oslanjaju samo na postojeće
klase u TYPO3 i/ili drugim ekstenzijama.</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.alttitle">Očisti privremeni spremnik (cache) nakon instalacije.</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.description">Ako je postavljena, EM će zahtijevati da se privremeni spremnik (cache) očisti kada se ova ekstenzija instalira.</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.alttitle">Postojeći tablice su promijenjene</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.description">Popis imena tablica koje ova ekstenzija samo mijenja, ne stvara ih.</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.details">Tablice iz ove liste pronađene u datoteci ekstenzije ext_tables.sql</label>
			<label index=".alttitle">EM</label>
			<label index=".description">Menadžer ekstenzijama (EM)</label>
			<label index=".details">TYPO3 može se proširiti u bilo kojem smjeru bez gubitka
kompatibilnosti unazad. API za ekstenzije pruža moćnu strukturu
za lagano dodavanje, oduzimanje, instalaciju i razvoj takvih
ekstenzija u TYPO3 okruženju. To posebno omogućava menadžer
ekstenzija EM unutat TYPO3.

&quot;Ekstenzije&quot; su pojam koje u TYPO3 pokriva dva druga pojma,
plugin-ovi i moduli.

Plugin je dio koji ima ulogu u samom web sjedištu.
Npr. oglasna ploča, knjiga gostiju, dućan itd. Uobičajeno je sadržan
unutar PHP klase i pozvan kroz USER ili USER_INT cObject
iz TypoScript-a. Plugin je ekstenzija u frontend-u.

Modul je backend aplikacija koja ima vlastitu poziciju u administracijskom
meniju. Zahtijeva prijavu na backend sustav i djeluje unutar strukture
beckenda. Također modulom možemo nazvati ako iskorištava
bilo kakvu povezivost nekog postojećeg modula, tj. ako se dodaje
meniju funkcija postojećih modula. Modul je ekstenzija u backend-u.</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.alttitle">Privatno</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.description">Ako je postavljeno, ova verzija se ne pokazuje u javnoj listi online repozitorij.</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.details">&quot;Privatni&quot;  uploadi zahtjevaju da ručno unesete posebni ključ (koji će vam se prikazati
nakon što se upload završi) da bi mogli importirati i pregledavati detalje uploadane ekstenzije.
To je zgodno kad radite na internim stvarima koje ne želite da drugi pregledavaju.
Možete postaviti i maknuti zastavicu privatno svaki put kada uploadate ekstenziju.</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.alttitle">Download zaporke</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.description">Dodatna zaporka je potrebna za download privatne ekstenzije.</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.details">Svi koji poznaju &quot;poseban ključ&quot; dodijeljen privatnom uploadu mogu taj upload importirati. Specificiranje zaporke za importiranje omogućava vam da podijelite ključ za download privatnih uploada ali i dodatno zahtjevate spomenutu zaporku.Zaporka se može kasnije promijeniti.</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.alttitle">Tip instalacije</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.description">Tip instalacije</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.details">Datoteke pojedine ekstenzije spremljene su u direktorij nazvan po ključu ekstenzije. Mjesto ovog direktorija može biti
unutar typo3/sysext/, typo3/ext/ , ili typo3conf/ext. Ekstenzija mora biti programirana tako da automatski otkriva
gdje je smještena i da može rasditi sa sve tri lokacije.

&lt;b&gt;  Lokalni smještaj “typo3conf/ext/”:&lt;/b&gt; Ovdje se spremaju ekstenzije koje su lokalne za pojedinu TYPO3 instalaciju.
Direktorij typo3conf/ je uvijek lokalan, i sadrži lokalnu konfiguraciju (npr. localconf.php), lokalne module, itd.
Ako ovdje smjestite ekstenziju biti će dostupna samo ovoj TYPO3 instalaciji.
To je &quot;po-bazi-podataka&quot; način instalacije ekstenzije.

&lt;b&gt;Globalni smještaj “typo3/ext/”:&lt;/b&gt; Ovdje se spremaju ekstenzije koje su globalne za TYPO3 izvorni kod na web
poslužitelju. Ove ekstenzije će biti dostupne za sve TYPO3 instalacije koje dijele izvorni kod.
Kada ažurirate vaš TYPO3 izvorni kod prikladno je kopirati typo3/ext direktorij iz prijašnje u obnovljenu instalaciju,
nadjačavši preddefinirani direktorij. Na taj će se način sve korištene globalne ekstenzije naći unutar novog izvornog koda.
Nakon toga uvijek možete ulaskom u TYPO3 po potrebi ažurirati inačice.
To je &quot;po-serveru&quot; način instalacije ekstenzije.

&lt;b&gt; Sistemski smještaj “typo3/sysext/”:&lt;/b&gt; Ovo su sistemski zadane ekstenzje  koje se nemogu i ne bi trebale ažurirati
od strane EM-a

&lt;b&gt; Prioriteti učitavanja&lt;/b&gt;
Lokalne ekstenzije imju prednost što znači da ukoliko ekstenzija postoji u typo3conf/ext/ i typo3/ext/ učitava
se samo ona iz typo3conf/ext/. Slično globalne ekstenzije imaju prednost nad sistemskim. To znači da se ekstenzije
učitavaju redosljedom lokalne-globalne-sistemske.
U praksi možete imati  &quot;stabilnu&quot; inačicu instaliranu u globalni direktorij (typo3/ext/), koju koriste svi vaši projekti
koji dijele izvorni kod na poslužitelju. S  druge strane na pojedinom pokusnom projektu možete importirati istu
ekstenziju u novijoj &quot;pokusnoj&quot; inačici, i za taj posebni projekt koristiti će se lokalno dostupne ekstenzije.</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.alttitle">Instalirana dva ili više puta?</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.description">Pokazuje ako je ekstenzija instalirana na više od jednog Sistemskog, Globalnog ili Lokalnog mjesta.</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.details">Kako ekstenzija može postojati na tri mjesta, Sistemsko, Globalno, Lokalno, ovo ukazuje nalaz li se ekstenzijai i na drugim mjestima osim trenutnog. U tom slučaju obratite pažnju koja je ekstenzija učitana!</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.alttitle">Početne datoteke</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.description">Popis datoteka u direktoriju ekstenzije. Ne prikazuje datoteka u poddirektorijima.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.alttitle">Zahtjevi bazi podataka</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.description">Ako postoje prikazuje zahtjeve tablicama i poljima baze podataka.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.details">Ovo će iz datoteka ext_tables.sql i ext_tables_static+adt.sql pročitati i prikazati koje su tablice, polja i statičke tablice potrebne ovoj ekstenziji.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.alttitle">Status zahtjeva bazi podataka.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.description">Prikazuje trenutni status baze podataka s obzirom na zahtjeve ekstenzije.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.details">Ako se ekstenzija učita pojaviti će se poruka greške ako potrebna polja ili tablice nisu prisutni u bazi podataka.</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.alttitle">Zastavice</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.description">Popis posebnih kodova koji vam govore na koje dijelove TYPO3 sustava ekstenzija utječe.</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.details">Ovo je popis zastavica:

&lt;b&gt;Module:&lt;/b&gt; Pravi backend main/sub modul je pronađen

&lt;b&gt;Module+:&lt;/b&gt; Ekstenzija dodaje samu sebe funkcijskom
meniju postojećeg backend modula

&lt;b&gt;loadTCA:&lt;/b&gt; Ekstenzija sadrži funkcijski poziv prema
t3lib_div::loadTCA za učitavanje tablice. To potencijalno može
usporiti sistem zato jer je potpun opis tablice uvijek uključen u
samu tablicu. U svakom slučaju vjerojatno postoji dobar razlog
za takav postupak Vjerojatno ekstenzija pokušava manipulirati
TCA-config za postojeću tablicu kako bi je proširila.

&lt;b&gt;TCA:&lt;/b&gt; Ekstenzija sadrži konfiguraciju tablice u $TCA.

&lt;b&gt;Plugin:&lt;/b&gt; Ekstenzija dodaje frontend plugin listi pluginova
u Sadržajni Element tipa &quot;Dodaj Plugin&quot;

&lt;b&gt;Plugin/ST43:&lt;/b&gt; TypoScript kod za prikazivanje plugin-a
dodan je statičkom predlošku &quot;Sadržaj (osnovni)&quot;. &quot;Plugin&quot; i
&quot;Plugin/ST43&quot; se obično koriste zajedno.

&lt;b&gt;Page-TSconfig:&lt;/b&gt; Osnovna Stranica-TSconfig je dodana.

&lt;b&gt;TS/Setup:&lt;/b&gt; Osnovne TypoScript Postavke su dodane.

&lt;b&gt;TS/Constants:&lt;/b&gt; Osnovne TypoScript Konstante su dodane.</label>
			<label index="emconf_conf.description">Pokazuje da li ekstenzija ima predložak za daljnju konfiguraciju</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.alttitle">Statične TypoScript datoteke</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.description">Pokazuje koji TypoScript statične datoteke mogu biti prisutne.</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.details">Ako su datoteke ext_typoscript_constants.txt i/ili ext_typoscript_setup.txt pronađene u direktoriju ekstenzije, one se uključuju u hijerarhiju svih TypoScript predložaka u TYPO3 sustavu odmah nakon preostalih uključenih statičkih predložaka.</label>
			<label index="emconf_locallang.alttitle">locallang-datoteke</label>
			<label index="emconf_locallang.description">Prikazuje koje su datoteke nazvane &quot;locallang.php&quot; prisutne u direktoriju ekstenzije (rekurzivna pretraga). Takve datoteke se uobičajeno koriste da dodijele nizu $LOCAL_LANG  oznake koje se koriste u sistemskim jezicima.</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.alttitle">Imena Backend Modula</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.description">Pokazuje koja su imena modula pronađena unutar ekstenzije.</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.alttitle">Imena PHP klasa</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.description">Pokazuje koje su PHP klase pronađene u .php i .inc datotekama.</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.alttitle">Greške</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.description">Prikazuje otkrivene ozbiljne greške u ekstenziji.</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.alttitle">Greške pri imenovanju</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.description">Određene konvencije imenovanja odnose se na ekstenzije. Ovdje se prikazuju pronađena prekršenja.</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.details">Konvencije imenovanja definirane su u &quot;Inside TYPO3&quot; dokumentu. Da bi se davanje imena maksimalno pojednostavilo, pokušajte izbjeći &quot;underscore&quot; znak u vašim ključevima ekstenzija.</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="hu" type="array">
			<label index="emconf_shy.alttitle">Shy</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.description">Ha be van állítva, a kiterjesztés alapértelmezetten rejtett lesz a Bővítménykezelőben, mert ez alapértelmezett kiterjesztés vagy más valami lehet, amely nem annyira fontos.</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.details">Ezt a jelzőt akkor használd, ha a kiterjesztés 'kevésbé érdekes'
(ami nem jelenti azt, hogy nem fontos - csak a kiterjesztés
ritkán használatos...)
Ez nem érinti azt, hogy ez engedélyezve van-e vagy sem.
Csak a Bővítménykezelőben látható.
Hagyományosan a shy egy a TYPO3_CONF_VARS-nak
megfelelő alapértelmezetten betöltődő kiterjesztéshalmaz.</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.alttitle">Kategória</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.description">Melyik kategóriához tartozzon a kiterjesztés.</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.details">&lt;b&gt;be:&lt;/b&gt; Backend (általánosan backend orientált, de nem modul)

&lt;b&gt;modul:&lt;/b&gt; Backend modulok (amikor valami egy modul vagy ahhoz csatlakozik)

&lt;b&gt;fe:&lt;/b&gt; Frontend (általánosan backend orientált, de nem ?valódi? beépülő)

&lt;b&gt;bővítmény:&lt;/b&gt; Frontend beépülők (?Beszúrt beépülő?tartalmi elemként beszúrt beépülő)

&lt;b&gt;vegyes:&lt;/b&gt; Vegyes dolog (máshova nem besorolt)

&lt;b&gt;példa:&lt;/b&gt; péda kiterjesztés (példaként stb. szolgálnak)</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.alttitle">Függések más kiterjesztésektől</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.description">Ez egy egyéb kiterjesztés kulcslista, amelynek tartalma a már korábban betöltött kiterjesztésektől függ.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.details">A Bővítménykezelő kezeli a localconf.php-ba íródó kiterjesztések függőségeit.</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.alttitle">Ütközések más kiterjesztésekkel?</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.description">Kiterjesztések kucslistája, amellyel a kiterjesztés nem dolgozik össze (és így nem engedélyezhetőek csak a megfelelő kiterjesztés törlésével)</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.alttitle">Lekérdezett betöltési elsőbbség</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.description">Meghatározza a Bővítménykezelő számára, hogy a kiterjesztéseket a lista elejére tegye. Alapértelmezésként a végére helyezi.</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.alttitle">Betöltött backend modulok</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.description">Ha bármely, a kiterjesztéshez tartozó alkönyvtár tartalmaz backend modult, ezek a könyvtár nevek itt lesznek kilistázva.</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.details">Engedélyezi a Bővítménykezelőnek, hogy tudjon a modul létezéséről, ami fontos, mert a Bővítménykezelőnek frissíteni kell a modul conf.php fájlját azért, hogy helyesen tudja beállítani a TYPO3_MOD_PATH konstanst.</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.alttitle">Fejlesztési állapot</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.description">Jelzi, hogy a kiterjesztés milyen fejlesztési állapotban van.</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.details">&lt;b&gt;alfa&lt;/b&gt;
Nagyon kezdeti állapot. Valószinűleg még semmi sem történt.

&lt;b&gt;béta&lt;/b&gt;
Éppen fejlesztés alatt. Részben működhet, de még nem befejezett.

&lt;b&gt;stabil&lt;/b&gt;
Stabil és használat alatt a termékben

&lt;b&gt;kísérleti&lt;/b&gt;
Senki nem tudja, működik-e... Talán csak egy ötlet...

&lt;b&gt;teszt&lt;/b&gt;
Teszt kiterjesztés, koncepciókat mutat be stb.</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.alttitle">A magban belsőleg támogatott</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.description">Ez a jelző jelzi, hogy a mag forráskódja speciálisan tud a kiterjesztésről.</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.details">A szavak sorrendjében ennek a jelzőnek kell továbbítani azt
az üzenetet, hogy ?ez a kiterjesztés nem írható meg bizonyos
mag forráskód változtatás nélkül?.
Egy kiterjesztés nem tekinthető belsőnek csak azért, mert a
TYPO3 általános osztályai használják, azaz a t3lib/.-ből.
A valódi nem belső kiterjesztések azzal jellemezhetőek, hogy
megírhatóak a mag forráskód változtatása nélkül, csak
felhasználják a TYPO3 meglevő osztályait és/vagy
kiterjesztéseit, valamint kiterjesztés könyvtárában levő saját
szkripteket.</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.alttitle">Telepítés után a cache törlése</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.description">Ha be van állítva, a Bővítménykezelő kitakarítja a gyorsítótárat a kiterjesztés telepítésekor.</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.alttitle">Létező megváltozott táblák</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.description">Táblanevek listája, amelyeket ez a kiterjesztés csak módosít, de nem teljesen készít el.</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.details">A kiterjesztés ext_tables.sql fájljában található táblalista.</label>
			<label index=".alttitle">BK</label>
			<label index=".description">Bővítménykezelő (BK)</label>
			<label index=".details">ATYPO3 kiterjeszthető gyakorlatilag bármely irányban a felülről
kompatilbilitás elvesztése nélkül. A Kiterjesztési Programozói
Felület hatékony keretrendszert nyújt a TYPO3 részére az ilyen
kiterjesztések hozzáadásához, törléséhez, telepítéséhez,
fejlesztéséhez. Ezt a Bővítménykezelő (BK) hatékonyan
támogatja a TYPO3.on belűl.

A ?kiterjesztés? egy fogalom a TYPO3-on belűl, amely két
másik fogalmat takar, a bővítményt és a modult.

A bővítmény egy szerepet játszik el magán a webhelyen. Azaz
üzenőfalat, vendégkönyvet, boltot stb. Általában PHP osztályba
ágyazott és a USER vagy a USER_INT cObject-en keresztűl
hívja meg a TypoScript. A bővítmény a frontenden egy
kiterjesztés.

A modul egy backend alkalmazás, amelynek saját pozíciója
van az adminisztrációs menüben. Backend bejelentkezést
igényel és a backend keretrendszeren belül működik.
Meghívhatunk valamit modulként akkor is, ha ez bontja
egy létező modul kapcsolódását, ez egyszerűen behelyezi
önmagát a meglévő modulok függvény menüjébe. A modul
a backenden egy kiterjesztés.</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.alttitle">Privát</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.description">Ha be van állítva, ez a verzió nem jelenik meg az online tár nyilvános listájában.</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.details">A &quot;privát&quot; feltöltések egy olyan manuálisan begépelt kulcs
megadását igénylik (amely a feltöltés befejeztével megjelenik)
a feltöltött kiterjesztés importálásának vagy a részletek
megtekinthetőségének érdekében.
Ez egy nagyon klassz dolog, amikor valami belső dolgon
dolgozol és nem szeretnéd, ha ezt mások is látnák.
A privát jelzőt be- és kikapcsolhatod valahányszor
feltöltöd a kiterjesztésedet.</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.alttitle">Letöltési jelszó</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.description">Privát kiterjesztések letöltéséhez szükséges kiegészítő jelszó.</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.details">Aki ismeri a privát feltöltéshez rendelt kulcsot, importálhatja azt. Az import jelszó megadása a letöltési kulcsot adja meg és továbbiakban egy jelszó is szükséges. A jelszó a későbbiekben megváltoztatható.</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.alttitle">Telepítési típus</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.description">A telepítés típusa</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.details">A kiterjesztés fájljai a kiterjesztés kulcsa alapján elnevezett
könyvtárban vannak. E könyvtár helye vagy a  typo3/sysext/,
a typo3/ext/ vagy a typo3conf/ext/ valamelyike.
A kiterjesztésnek programozottnak kell lennie, így
automatikusan érzékeli, hogy hol található és működhet mind
a három helyről.

&lt;b&gt;Lokális hely ?typo3conf/ext/?:&lt;/b&gt; Itt találhatóak azok
a kiterjesztések, amelyek egy bizonyos TYPO3 telepítésre
nézve lokálisak. A typo3conf/ könyvtár mindig helyi, helyi
konfigurációt (lásd localconf.php), helyi modulokat stb.
tartalmaz. Az ide elhelyezett kiterjesztés csak ezen TYPO3
telepítés számára lesz elérhető. Ez az adatbázis telepítés
?adatbázis-alapú? módja.

&lt;b&gt;Globális hely ?typo3/ext/?:&lt;/b&gt; Itt olyan kiterjesztések
találhatóak, amelyek a TYPO3 forráskód szempontjából
globálisak a webszerveren. Ezek a kiterjesztések elérhetőek
bármelyik TYPO3 telepítés részére megosztva a forráskódot.
Ha frissül a TYPO3 forráskód, célszerű a régi typo3/ext/
könyvtárat átmásolni az új telepítésbe, felülírva az eredetit.
Ezen a módon az összes használatos globális kiterjesztés az
új verzió forráskódjában is megjelenik. Ezek után mindig lehet
frissíteni a kívánt verziókat. Ez az adatbázis telepítés
?szerver-alapú? módja.

&lt;b&gt;Rendszerszintű hely ?typo3/sysext/?:&lt;/b&gt; Ez a rendszer
alap kiterjesztéseinek a helye, amelyet nem lehet és nem
ajánlatos frissíteni a Kiterjesztés Menedzser segítségével.

&lt;b&gt;Betöltési elsőbbség:&lt;/b&gt; A helyi kiterjesztések egyfajta
elsőbbséggel bírnak, aza, ha egy kiterjesztés létezik mind a
typo3conf/ext/ and typo3/ext/ könyvtárban, akkor a
typo3conf/ext/ -beli töltődik be. Hasonlóan a globális
kiterjesztések szintén elsőbbséggel bírnak a rendszerszintű
kiterjesztésekkel szemben. Ez azt jelenti, hogy a kiterjesztések
a lokális-globális-rendszerszintű sorrendben töltődnek be.
Ilyen módon egy telepített kiterjesztésnek stabil verziója a
globális könyvtárban van (typo3/ext/), amelyet a szerveren
levő bármely projekt használhat megosztva a forráskódot, de
egy egyszerű kísérleti projektben ugyannak a kiterjesztésnek
egy újabb verziója importálható be a projektnek megfelelően
helyi kiterjesztésként a régebbi helyett.</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.alttitle">Kétszer vagy többször telepített?</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.description">Megmondja, hogy egy kiterjesztés telepítve van-e egynél többször a System, Global vagy Local helyek egyikében.</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.details">Mivel a kiterjesztés három helyen fordulhat elő (System, Global, Local), jelzi, ha a kiterjesztés a jelenleginél eltérő helyen található. Ebben az esetben ügyelni kell arra, hogy a kiterjesztések melyikét töltjük be.</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.alttitle">Gyökér fájlok</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.description">Fájlok listája a kiterjesztés könyvtárában. Nem listázza az alkönyvtárbakban levő fájlokat.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.alttitle">Adatbázis szükséges</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.description">Jelzi az adatbázis táblák és mezők szükségességét, ha van ilyen.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.details">Ez az ext_tables.sql és az ext_tables_static+adt.sql fájlokból kerül beolvasásra és megmutatja, mely táblák, mezők és statikus táblák szükségesek a kiterjesztés részére.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.alttitle">Adatbázis szükségességi állapot</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.description">Kijelzi az adatbázis jelen állapotát összevetve a szükséges kiterjesztésekkel.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.details">Ha egy kiterjesztés olyan töltődött be, amely hibaüzenetet jelenít meg, amennyiben bizonyos szükséges táblák és mezők nincsenek meg.</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.alttitle">Jelzők</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.description">Speciális kódolású lista, amely megmondja, hogy a kiterjesztés a TYPO3 mely részeit érinti.</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.details">Ez jelzőlista:

&lt;b&gt;Modul:&lt;/b&gt; Egy valódi backend főmodul vagy almodul
található hozzáadásra.

&lt;b&gt;Modul+:&lt;/b&gt; A kiterjesztés hozzáadja önmagát egy létező
backend modul funkciómenüjéhez.

&lt;b&gt;loadTCA:&lt;/b&gt; A kiterjesztés tartalmaz
egy t3lib_div::loadTCA  nevű függvényt egy tábla betöltésére.
Ez potenciálisan azt jelenti, hogy a rendszer lelassul, mert
valamely tábla teljes táblaleírása mindig betöltődik. Ennek meg
van a maga oka. A kiterjesztés megpróbálja manipulálni egy
létező tábla részére a TCA konfigurációt, hogy kiterjessze azt.

&lt;b&gt;TCA:&lt;/b&gt;  A kiterjesztés a $TCA-ban tartalmazza egy
tábla konfigurációját.

&lt;b&gt;Bővítmény:&lt;/b&gt; A kiterjesztés hozzáad egy frontend
beépülőt a Tartalmi Elemek &quot;Beszúrt bővítmények&quot; részének
bővítménylistájába.

&lt;b&gt;Bővítmény/ST43:&lt;/b&gt; TypoScript generált kód a bővítmény
részére, amely hozzáadódik a staikus &quot;Tartalom (alap)&quot;
sablonhoz. A &quot;Bővítmény&quot; és a &quot;Bővítmény/ST43&quot; általában együtt
használatos.

&lt;b&gt;Oldal-TSconfig:&lt;/b&gt; Alapértelmezett Oldal-TSconfig
hozzáadva.

&lt;b&gt;Felhasználó-TSconfig:&lt;/b&gt; Alapértelmezettt
Felhasználó-TSconfig hozzáadva.

&lt;b&gt;TS/Telepítés:&lt;/b&gt; Alapértelmezett TypoScript
telepítés hozzáadva.

&lt;b&gt;TS/Konstansok:&lt;/b&gt; Alapértelmezett TypoScript
konstansok hozzáadva.</label>
			<label index="emconf_conf.description">Jelzi, hogy a kiterjesztésnek van-e további alsószintű konfigurációs sablonja.</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.alttitle">Statikus TypoScript fájlok</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.description">Kijelzi. hogy mely statikus TypoScript fájlok vannak jelen.</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.details">Ha a ext_typoscript_constants.txt és/vagy ext_typoscript_setup.txt fájlok megtalálhatóak a kiterjesztés könyvtárában, akkor ezek beépülnek a TYPO3 összes TypoScript sablon hierarhiájába közvetlenül a más statikus sablonokba való beépülés után.</label>
			<label index="emconf_locallang.alttitle">locallang file-ok</label>
			<label index="emconf_locallang.description">Kijelzi, hogy a helyi nyelvi fájlnak nevezett fájlok vannak jelen a kiterjesztés könyvtárában (rekurzív kereséssel). Az ilyen fájlok rendszerint a $LOCAL_LANG tömb címkéit jelenítik meg a rendszer nyelvének megfelelően.</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.alttitle">Backend modul nevek</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.description">Kijelzi, melyik modulnév található a kiterjesztésen belül.</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.alttitle">PHP osztály nevek</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.description">Kijelzi, hogy mely PHP osztályok találhatóak a .php és .inc fájlokban.</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.alttitle">Hibák</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.description">Kijelzi, ha valamilyen komoly hiba merült fel a kiterjesztéssel kapcsolatban.</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.alttitle">Névhely hibák</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.description">Bizonyos névkonvenciókat alkalmaz a kiterjesztésekre. Kijelzi, ha bármilyen ütközés merült fel.</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.details">A névkonverziók az &quot;Inside TYPO3&quot; dokumentumban olvashatóak. Próbálj a lehető legegyszerűbb elnevezést adni, lehetőleg nem alkalmazva az aláhúzás jelet ( _ ).</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="gl" type="array">
			<label index="emconf_shy.alttitle">Toqqoqqasoq</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="th" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="gr" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="hk" type="array">
			<label index="emconf_shy.alttitle">隱藏</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.description">假如設定了，延伸工具正常會在延伸工具管理員中被隱藏，因為它可能是一個預設的延伸工具或不然是一些不很重要的東西</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.details">假如一個延伸工具不是太引起興趣（不同於不重要 - 只是一個不常有人尋找的延伸工具），就使用這個標記
這不影響延伸工具是否啟動。只是在延伸工具管理員中顯示。正常的說，根據TYPO3_CONF_VARS，所有預設載入的延伸工具都設定為隱藏</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.alttitle">類別</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.description">延伸工具所屬類別</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.details">&lt;b&gt;be:&lt;/b&gt;後勤
（一般為後勤導向，但並非模組）

&lt;b&gt;module:&lt;/b&gt;後勤模組（當有些東西是模組或連接到模組）

&lt;b&gt;fe:&lt;/b&gt;前置
（一般為前置插入式裝置）


&lt;b&gt;plugin:&lt;/b&gt;前置插入式裝置（插入式裝置被加入為元件）

&lt;b&gt;misc:&lt;/b&gt;其他（不能輕易分類）

&lt;b&gt;example:&lt;/b&gt;延伸工具範例（作為範例等）</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.alttitle">其他延伸工具的相依性？</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.description">這個延伸工具所倚賴的其他延伸工具鑰字名單，在載入自己前先載入此名單</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.details">當把延伸工具名單寫進 localconf.php 時，延伸工具管理員會處理相依性</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.alttitle">與其他延伸工具衝突？</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.description">不能與這個延伸工具一起運作的延伸工具鑰字名單（因此在這些工具不被解除安裝之前，延伸工具不能夠被啟動）</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.alttitle">要求載入優先性</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.description">通知延伸工具管理員嘗試把延伸工具放到名單的最前面。預設是放到最後的</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.alttitle">被包括的後勤模組</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.description">假如任何一個延伸工具的子資料夾包含後勤模組，這些資料夾的名稱應會在這裡被列出</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.details">容許「延伸工具管理員」知道模組的存在，是重要的，因為「延伸工具管理員」為了設定正確的TYPO3_MOD_PATH常值，需要更新模組的conf.php檔</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.alttitle">發展狀態</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.description">延伸工具處於那一個發展狀態</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.details">&lt;b&gt;alpha&lt;/b&gt;
非常初期的發展。
也許完全不做任何事。

&lt;b&gt;beta&lt;/b&gt;
正在發展中
應該有限地運作,但是仍未完成

&lt;b&gt;stable&lt;/b&gt;
穩定和可完全運作

&lt;b&gt;experimental&lt;/b&gt;
還沒有人知道會發生甚麼事...也許仍是只是一個意念

&lt;b&gt;test&lt;/b&gt;
測試延伸工具，顯示概念等</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.alttitle">在核心內部支援</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.description">這記號指出核心源碼是特別地留意延這個延伸工具</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.alttitle">當安裝時，清除快取檔案</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.description">假如設定了，當安裝延伸工具時，延伸工具管理員就會要求清除快取檔案</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.alttitle">現存資料表被修改</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.description">只能夠被這個延伸工具修改（不是完全的建立）的資料表名稱的名單</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.details">在延伸工具的ext_tables.sql檔案中找到的這個名單中的資料表</label>
			<label index=".alttitle">EM</label>
			<label index=".description">延伸工具管理員(EM）</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.alttitle">私人</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.description">假如定了，這個版本不會顯示於線上收藏庫的公開名單中</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.alttitle">下載密碼</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.description">要下載私人延伸工具就需要附加的密碼</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.alttitle">安裝類型</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.description">安裝類型</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.alttitle">安裝兩次或以上？</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.description">通知你延伸工具是否在系統中安裝多於一次，全體地或本地位置</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.details">因為一個延伸工具可以處身於三個位置，系統﹑整體和本地，這指出延伸工具是否被發現處身於現有位置以外。在這情況下你應該意那一個延伸工具已經被載入。</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.alttitle">根檔案</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.description">在延伸工具中的檔案名單。沒有列出子資料夾中的檔案</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.alttitle">資料庫要求</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.description">向你顯示對資料庫表格和欄的要求（如有）</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.details">這會從ext_tables.sql 檔和 ext_tables_static+adt.sql 檔讀入，並且向你顯示延伸工具需要那些資料表﹑欄位和靜態料表</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.alttitle">資料庫要求狀況</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.description">顯示資料庫的目前狀態，與延伸工具所要求的作比較</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.details">假如延伸工具被載入，假如有資料表或欄並不如所料出現在資料庫中就會顯示錯誤訊息</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.alttitle">記號</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.description">特別碼的名單，它們會告訴你有關延伸工具會觸及TYPO3的那些部分</label>
			<label index="emconf_conf.description">顯示延伸工具是否有樣版以進行更低層次的設定</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.alttitle">靜態的TypoScript檔案</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.description">顯示那一個TypoScript靜態檔案會出現</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.details">假如ext_typoscript_constants.txt檔和／或 ext_typoscript_setup.txt在延伸工具的資料夾被發現，他們就被括在TYPO3所有TypoScript樣版的階級組識中，就在其他靜態樣版的內容之後</label>
			<label index="emconf_locallang.alttitle">locallang-files</label>
			<label index="emconf_locallang.description">顯示那一些命稱為「locallang.php」的檔案出現於延伸工具的資料夾中（遞進的搜尋）。這些檔案一般出現於一個array$LOCAL_LANG，內有系統語言的標籤</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.alttitle">後勤模組名稱</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.description">顯示在延伸工具中找到那個模組</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.alttitle">PHP Class 名稱</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.description">顯示在.php 和 .inc 檔案中找到那些 PHP-Class</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.alttitle">錯誤</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.description">顯示有否發現延伸工具有任何嚴重的錯誤</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.alttitle">名稱空隔錯誤</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.description">某些命名方法應用到延伸工具。這顯示發現到的任何不符</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.details">命名方法在「Inside TYPO3」中已定義了。為了使命名盡量簡單，嘗試避免在你的延伸工具鑰字中加上底線</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="eu" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="bg" type="array">
			<label index="emconf_shy.alttitle">Shy</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.description">Ако е сложено, разширението обикновенно ще е скрито в МР, защото може да е по-подразбиране или в друг случай нещо което не е толкова важно.</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.details">Използвайте този флаг ако разрешение е с  'рядък интерест'
(което не е същото като неважен - просто разширение което
 не е често търсено...)
Това не засяга дали е или не е позволено (enabled)
разширението.
Само е показано в МР.
Обикновенно &quot;shy&quot; е сложено за всички заредени
по-подразбиране разширения съобразно с TYPO3_CONF_VARS.</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.alttitle">Категория</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.description">Към коя категория принадлежи разширението (extension).</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.details">&lt;b&gt;be:&lt;/b&gt; Backend (Обикновенно backend ориентирано, но не модул)

&lt;b&gt;модул:&lt;/b&gt; Backend модули (Когато нещо е модул или е свързано с един модул)

&lt;b&gt;fe:&lt;/b&gt; Frontend (Обикновенно frontend ориентиран, но не &quot;истински&quot; plugin)

&lt;b&gt;plugin:&lt;/b&gt; Frontend plugins (Plugins вмъкнат като “Вмъкнат Plugin” елемент на съдържание)

&lt;b&gt;misc:&lt;/b&gt; Различни неща (Където другаде не лесно сложени)

&lt;b&gt;пример:&lt;/b&gt; Примерно разширение ( Който служат като примери др.)</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.alttitle">Зависимост от други разширения (extension)?</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.description">Това е списък с други ключове на разширения от който тези разширения зависят ПРЕДИ да бъдат заредени самите те.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.details">МР ще управлява тази зависимост докато се записва списъка на разширенията в localconf.php</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.alttitle">Конфликт с други разширения (extension)?</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.description">Списък на ключове на разширения с който те не работят (и така не могат да бъдат използвани преди другите не бъдат деинсталирани)</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.alttitle">Искания приоритет при зареждане</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.description">Това казва на МР да опита да сложи разширението на първото място в списъка. По-подразбиране е последното.</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.alttitle">включително Backend модули</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.description">Ако някоя подпапка към разширение съдържа backend модули, имената на тези папки трябва да са изписани тук.</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.details">Това позволява на МР да знае за съществуването на модули, който са важни защото МР трябва да обнови файла conf.php на модула за да сложи правилната TYPO3_MOD_PATH константа.</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.alttitle">Състояние на развитието (Development state)</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.description">В какво състояние на развитие се намира разширението.</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.details">&lt;b&gt;алфа&lt;/b&gt;
Много първоначално развитие. Може да не прави нищо.

&lt;b&gt;бета&lt;/b&gt;
Под текущо развитие. Трябва да работи от части, но не е завършено все още.

&lt;b&gt;стабилно&lt;/b&gt;
Стабилно и използвано в производство .

&lt;b&gt;експериментално&lt;/b&gt;
Никой незнае дали това отива нанякаде... Може би е все още само идея.

&lt;b&gt;тест&lt;/b&gt;
Тестово разширение, демонстриращо идея и др.</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.alttitle">Вътрешно поддържано в ядрото</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.description">Този флаг показва че, изходния код на ядрото е специално наясно с разширението.</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.alttitle">Изчисти кеша когато се инсталира</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.description">Ако е сложено, МР ще поиска да се изчисти кеша след като се е инсталирало разширението.</label>
			<label index=".alttitle">МР</label>
			<label index=".description">Менажера на разширения (МР)</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.alttitle">Частно</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.alttitle">Свали паролата</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.alttitle">Тип на инсталацията</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.description">Типа на инсталацията</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.alttitle">Два пъти или повече инсталирано?</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.alttitle">Изисквания на базата данни</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.alttitle">Статус на изискванията на базата данни</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.alttitle">Флагове</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.alttitle">Статични TypoScript файлове</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.alttitle">PHP Class имена</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.description">Покажи кой PHP-класове са намерени в .php и .inc файлове.</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.alttitle">Грешки</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="br" type="array">
			<label index="emconf_shy.alttitle">Oculta</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.description">Quando selecionada, esta extensão normalmente é oculta no AE por ser considerada uma extensão padrão, ou por algum outro motivo de menor importância.</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.details">Use esta opção se uma extensão for de &quot;raro interesse&quot; (o que não significa que seja de pouca importância - apenas uma extensão procurada com pouca freqüência...)
Esta opção não determina se a extensão está ou não ativada, apenas determina a visualização no AE.
Normalmente a opção &quot;oculta&quot; é usada em todas as extensões carregadas por padrão, conforme TYPO3_CONF_VARS.</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.alttitle">Categoria</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.description">Categoria à qual a extensão pertence.</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.details">&lt;b&gt;be:&lt;/b&gt; Administração do Site (Geralmente orientada pela administração do site, mas não é um módulo)

&lt;b&gt;módulo:&lt;/b&gt; Módulos de administração do site (Quando algo é um módulo ou se conecta a algum)

&lt;b&gt;fe:&lt;/b&gt; Site (Geralmente orientado pelo site, mas não um plugin &quot;real&quot;)

&lt;b&gt;plugin&lt;/b&gt; Plugins do site (Plugins inseridos como um elemento de conteúdo &quot;Inserir Plugin&quot;)

&lt;b&gt;misc:&lt;/b&gt; Artigos de Miscelânea (Não podem ser facilmente colocados em outro lugar)

&lt;b&gt;exemplo:&lt;/b&gt; Extensão de exemplo (Que serve como um exemplo, etc.)</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.alttitle">Depende de outras extensões?</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.description">Esta é uma lista das extensões das quais esta extensão depende que sejam carregadas ANTES dela.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.details">O AE estabelecerá tal dependência ao gravar a lista de extensões em localconf.php</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.alttitle">Gera conflito com outras extensões?</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.description">Lista de extensões com as quais esta extensão não funciona (e portanto não pode ser ativada antes que as outras sejam desinstaladas)</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.alttitle">Prioridade para carregamento da extensão</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.description">Esta opção avisa ao AE para tentar carregar a extensão como a primeira da lista. O padrão é carregá-la por último.</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.alttitle">Módulos de administração inclusos</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.description">Se alguma subpasta de uma extensão contiver módulos de administração, os nomes das subpastas serão listados aqui.</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.details">Informa ao AE sobre a existência do módulo, o que é importante já que o AE precisa atualizar o arquivo conf.php do módulo para atribuir corretamente a constante TYPO3_MOD_PATH.</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.alttitle">Status de desenvolvimento</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.description">Em qual status de desenvolvimento a extensão se encontra.</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.details">&lt;b&gt;alfa&lt;/b&gt;
Desenvolvimento em fase inicial. A extensão pode não estar executando qualquer função.

&lt;b&gt;beta&lt;/b&gt;
Sob desenvolvimento. Pode estar funcionando parcialmente, mas não está concluída.

&lt;b&gt;estável&lt;/b&gt;
Estável e utilizada normalmente em produção.

&lt;b&gt;experimental&lt;/b&gt;
Não se sabe se vai chegar a algum lugar... Talvez seja ainda apenas uma idéia.

&lt;b&gt;teste&lt;/b&gt;
Extensão para teste, para demonstrar conceitos, etc.</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.alttitle">Internamente suportado pelo núcleo</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.description">Esta nota indica que o código fonte do núcleo está especificamente ciente desta extensão.</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.details">Em outras palavras, esta marca nota deveria tratar sobre a mensagem &quot;esta extensão não pode ser escrita sem algumas modificações do código fonte do núcleo&quot;.

Uma extensão não é interna só porque usa as classes gerais do TYPO3, por exemplo, aquelas da pasta t3lib/. É claro que extensões não-internas são caracterizadas pelo fato de que elas poderiam ser escritas sem fazer mudanças no código fonte do núcleo, mas depende apenas de classes existentes no TYPO3 e/ou outras extensões, além de seus próprios scripts na pasta de extensões.</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.alttitle">Limpar o cache quando instalada</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.description">Quando selecionada, o AE solicitará a limpeza do cache quando esta extensão for instalada.</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.alttitle">Tabelas existentes modificadas</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.description">Lista de tabelas que apenas foram modificadas - não criadas a partir do zero - por esta extensão.</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.details">Tabelas desta lista encontradas no arquivo ext_tables.sql desta extensão</label>
			<label index=".alttitle">AE</label>
			<label index=".description">O Administrador de Extensões (AE)</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.alttitle">Particular</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.description">Se marcado, esta versão não é mostrada na lista pública do repositório online.</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.details">Uploads &quot;Particulares&quot; requerem que você manualmente digite uma chave especial (que será mostrada para você depois que o upload terminar) para ser possível importar e ver os detalhes da extensão enviada. Isso é bom para quando trabalha-se com algo internamente e não quer que outros vejam. Você pode marcar e desmarcar a caixa cada vez que enviar uma extensão.</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.alttitle">Senha para download</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.description">Senha adicional necessária para baixar extensões particulares.</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.details">Qualquer um que conhece a &quot;chave especial&quot;, atribuída ao upload particular, poderá importá-lo. Especificar uma senha para upload permite que você tire a chave de download para uploads particulares dados. A senha pode ser mudada mais tarde.</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.alttitle">Tipo de instalação</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.description">O tipo da instalação</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.alttitle">Instalado duas vezes ou mais?</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.description">Diz se a extensão está instalada em mais de uma localidade: Sistema, Global ou Localmente.</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.details">Devido a uma extensão residir em três localidades, Sistema, Global e Local, isso indica se a extensão é achada em outros lugares, além do atual. Nesse caso, você deve estar ciente de qual delas está carregada!</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.alttitle">Arquivos da raiz</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.description">Lista dos arquivos no diretório da extensão. Não lista arquivos em subdiretórios.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.alttitle">Necessidades do Banco de Dados</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.description">Mostra as necessidades para as tabelas e campos do banco de dados, se tiver algum.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.details">Isso irá ler o arquivo ext_tables.sql e ext_tables_static+adt.sql e mostrar a você quais tabelas, campos e tabelas estáticas são requeridas com esta extensão.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.alttitle">Situação de necessidades do banco de dados</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.description">Mostra a estatística atual do banco de dados, comparado às necessidades da extensão.</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.details">Se a extensão está carregada, qual irá mostrar uma mensagem de erro, se alguma das tabelas ou campos não se apresentarem no banco de dados como eles deveriam ser!</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.alttitle">Marcas</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.description">Uma lista de códigos especiais que dizem a você algo sobre quais partes de TYPO3 a extensão toca.</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.alttitle">Erros</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="et" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ar" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="he" type="array">
			<label index="emconf_category.alttitle">קטגוריה</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ua" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="lv" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="jp" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="vn" type="array">
		</languageKey>
	</data>
	<orig_hash type="array">
		<languageKey index="default" type="array">
			<label index="emconf_shy.alttitle" type="integer">217108965</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.description" type="integer">196807582</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.details" type="integer">206691994</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.alttitle" type="integer">61717939</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.description" type="integer">204987594</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.details" type="integer">246335601</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.alttitle" type="integer">6158334</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.description" type="integer">262753637</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.details" type="integer">54343024</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.alttitle" type="integer">174778315</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.description" type="integer">14159431</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.alttitle" type="integer">208790249</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.description" type="integer">261230598</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.alttitle" type="integer">222311525</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.description" type="integer">131352939</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.details" type="integer">16797237</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.alttitle" type="integer">8968835</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.description" type="integer">48322308</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.details" type="integer">80752734</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.alttitle" type="integer">252258090</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.description" type="integer">130243565</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.details" type="integer">242835609</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.alttitle" type="integer">26668595</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.description" type="integer">149991239</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.alttitle" type="integer">211801845</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.description" type="integer">225814359</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.details" type="integer">250561664</label>
			<label index=".alttitle" type="integer">194364373</label>
			<label index=".description" type="integer">17437649</label>
			<label index=".details" type="integer">238023326</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.alttitle" type="integer">75468930</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.description" type="integer">8590515</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.details" type="integer">183041250</label>
			<label index="_emconf_private.seeAlso" type="integer">246806958</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.alttitle" type="integer">102196861</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.description" type="integer">120757501</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.details" type="integer">92160698</label>
			<label index="_emconf_download_password.seeAlso" type="integer">211543191</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.alttitle" type="integer">121209022</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.description" type="integer">113056504</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.details" type="integer">147333350</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.alttitle" type="integer">262159324</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.description" type="integer">60133779</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.details" type="integer">201896892</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.alttitle" type="integer">234183730</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.description" type="integer">157844662</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.alttitle" type="integer">28332369</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.description" type="integer">93463627</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.details" type="integer">199359275</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.alttitle" type="integer">204171626</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.description" type="integer">166393559</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.details" type="integer">198198907</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.alttitle" type="integer">82475009</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.description" type="integer">42715313</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.details" type="integer">209778452</label>
			<label index="emconf_conf.description" type="integer">49196456</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.alttitle" type="integer">43118947</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.description" type="integer">196469558</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.details" type="integer">238768833</label>
			<label index="emconf_locallang.alttitle" type="integer">182381040</label>
			<label index="emconf_locallang.description" type="integer">112585123</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.alttitle" type="integer">70637876</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.description" type="integer">207879145</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.alttitle" type="integer">155053783</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.description" type="integer">83027952</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.alttitle" type="integer">99552371</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.description" type="integer">88544755</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.alttitle" type="integer">190879862</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.description" type="integer">168628900</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.details" type="integer">76599956</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.syntax" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_shy.seeAlso" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_shy.image" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.image_descr" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.syntax" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_category.seeAlso" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_category.image" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.image_descr" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.syntax" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_dependencies.seeAlso" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_dependencies.image" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.image_descr" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.details" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.syntax" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_conflicts.seeAlso" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_conflicts.image" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.image_descr" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.details" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.syntax" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_priority.seeAlso" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_priority.image" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.image_descr" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.syntax" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_module.seeAlso" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_module.image" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.image_descr" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.syntax" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_state.seeAlso" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_state.image" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.image_descr" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.syntax" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_internal.seeAlso" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_internal.image" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.image_descr" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.details" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.syntax" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.seeAlso" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.image" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.image_descr" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.syntax" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_modify_tables.seeAlso" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_modify_tables.image" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.image_descr" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index=".syntax" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_.seeAlso" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_.image" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index=".image_descr" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.syntax" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_private.image" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.image_descr" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.syntax" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_download_password.image" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.image_descr" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.syntax" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_type.seeAlso" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_type.image" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.image_descr" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.syntax" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_doubleInstall.seeAlso" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_doubleInstall.image" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.image_descr" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.details" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.syntax" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_rootfiles.seeAlso" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_rootfiles.image" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.image_descr" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.syntax" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_dbReq.seeAlso" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_dbReq.image" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.image_descr" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.syntax" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_dbStatus.seeAlso" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_dbStatus.image" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.image_descr" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.syntax" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_flags.seeAlso" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_flags.image" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.image_descr" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_conf.alttitle" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_conf.details" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_conf.syntax" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_conf.seeAlso" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_conf.image" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_conf.image_descr" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.syntax" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_TSfiles.seeAlso" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_TSfiles.image" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.image_descr" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_locallang.details" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_locallang.syntax" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_locallang.seeAlso" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_locallang.image" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_locallang.image_descr" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.details" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.syntax" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_moduleNames.seeAlso" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_moduleNames.image" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.image_descr" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.details" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.syntax" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_classNames.seeAlso" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_classNames.image" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.image_descr" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.details" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.syntax" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_errors.seeAlso" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_errors.image" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.image_descr" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.syntax" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_NSerrors.seeAlso" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="_emconf_NSerrors.image" type="integer">222419149</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.image_descr" type="integer">222419149</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="dk" type="array">
			<label index="emconf_shy.alttitle" type="integer">217108965</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.description" type="integer">196807582</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.details" type="integer">206691994</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.alttitle" type="integer">61717939</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.description" type="integer">204987594</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.details" type="integer">149403635</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.alttitle" type="integer">6158334</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.description" type="integer">262753637</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.details" type="integer">54343024</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.alttitle" type="integer">174778315</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.description" type="integer">14159431</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.alttitle" type="integer">208790249</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.description" type="integer">261230598</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.alttitle" type="integer">222311525</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.description" type="integer">131352939</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.details" type="integer">16797237</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.alttitle" type="integer">8968835</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.description" type="integer">48322308</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.details" type="integer">170748201</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.alttitle" type="integer">252258090</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.description" type="integer">130243565</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.details" type="integer">78637286</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.alttitle" type="integer">26668595</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.description" type="integer">149991239</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.alttitle" type="integer">211801845</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.description" type="integer">225814359</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.details" type="integer">155805870</label>
			<label index=".alttitle" type="integer">194364373</label>
			<label index=".description" type="integer">17437649</label>
			<label index=".details" type="integer">238023326</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.alttitle" type="integer">75468930</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.description" type="integer">8590515</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.details" type="integer">183041250</label>
			<label index="_emconf_private.seeAlso" type="integer">246806958</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.alttitle" type="integer">102196861</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.description" type="integer">120757501</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.details" type="integer">92160698</label>
			<label index="_emconf_download_password.seeAlso" type="integer">211543191</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.alttitle" type="integer">121209022</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.description" type="integer">113056504</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.details" type="integer">179328140</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.alttitle" type="integer">262159324</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.description" type="integer">60133779</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.details" type="integer">201896892</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.alttitle" type="integer">234183730</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.description" type="integer">157844662</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.alttitle" type="integer">28332369</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.description" type="integer">93463627</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.details" type="integer">199359275</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.alttitle" type="integer">204171626</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.description" type="integer">166393559</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.details" type="integer">198198907</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.alttitle" type="integer">82475009</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.description" type="integer">42715313</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.details" type="integer">54918453</label>
			<label index="emconf_conf.description" type="integer">49196456</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.alttitle" type="integer">43118947</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.description" type="integer">196469558</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.details" type="integer">238768833</label>
			<label index="emconf_locallang.alttitle" type="integer">182381040</label>
			<label index="emconf_locallang.description" type="integer">112585123</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.alttitle" type="integer">70637876</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.description" type="integer">207879145</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.alttitle" type="integer">155053783</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.description" type="integer">83027952</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.alttitle" type="integer">99552371</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.description" type="integer">88544755</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.alttitle" type="integer">190879862</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.description" type="integer">168628900</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.details" type="integer">76599956</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="de" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="no" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="it" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="fr" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="es" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="nl" type="array">
			<label index="emconf_shy.alttitle" type="integer">217108965</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.description" type="integer">196807582</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.details" type="integer">206691994</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.alttitle" type="integer">61717939</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.description" type="integer">204987594</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.details" type="integer">149403635</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.alttitle" type="integer">6158334</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.description" type="integer">262753637</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.details" type="integer">54343024</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.alttitle" type="integer">174778315</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.description" type="integer">14159431</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.alttitle" type="integer">208790249</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.description" type="integer">261230598</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.alttitle" type="integer">222311525</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.description" type="integer">131352939</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.details" type="integer">16797237</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.alttitle" type="integer">8968835</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.description" type="integer">48322308</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.details" type="integer">170748201</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.alttitle" type="integer">252258090</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.description" type="integer">130243565</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.details" type="integer">78637286</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.alttitle" type="integer">26668595</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.description" type="integer">149991239</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.alttitle" type="integer">211801845</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.description" type="integer">225814359</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.details" type="integer">155805870</label>
			<label index=".alttitle" type="integer">194364373</label>
			<label index=".description" type="integer">17437649</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.alttitle" type="integer">70637876</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.alttitle" type="integer">99552371</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.alttitle" type="integer">190879862</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="cz" type="array">
			<label index="emconf_shy.alttitle" type="integer">217108965</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.description" type="integer">196807582</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.details" type="integer">206691994</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="pl" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="si" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="fi" type="array">
			<label index="emconf_shy.alttitle" type="integer">217108965</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.description" type="integer">196807582</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.details" type="integer">206691994</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.alttitle" type="integer">61717939</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.description" type="integer">204987594</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.details" type="integer">149403635</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.alttitle" type="integer">6158334</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.description" type="integer">262753637</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.details" type="integer">54343024</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.alttitle" type="integer">174778315</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.description" type="integer">14159431</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.alttitle" type="integer">208790249</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.description" type="integer">261230598</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.alttitle" type="integer">222311525</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.description" type="integer">131352939</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.details" type="integer">16797237</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.alttitle" type="integer">8968835</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.description" type="integer">48322308</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.details" type="integer">170748201</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.alttitle" type="integer">252258090</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.description" type="integer">130243565</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.details" type="integer">78637286</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.alttitle" type="integer">26668595</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.description" type="integer">149991239</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.alttitle" type="integer">211801845</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.description" type="integer">225814359</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.details" type="integer">155805870</label>
			<label index=".alttitle" type="integer">194364373</label>
			<label index=".description" type="integer">17437649</label>
			<label index=".details" type="integer">238023326</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.alttitle" type="integer">75468930</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.description" type="integer">8590515</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.details" type="integer">183041250</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.alttitle" type="integer">102196861</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.description" type="integer">120757501</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.details" type="integer">92160698</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.alttitle" type="integer">121209022</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.description" type="integer">113056504</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.details" type="integer">179328140</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.alttitle" type="integer">262159324</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.description" type="integer">60133779</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.details" type="integer">201896892</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.alttitle" type="integer">234183730</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.description" type="integer">157844662</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.alttitle" type="integer">28332369</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.description" type="integer">93463627</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.details" type="integer">199359275</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.alttitle" type="integer">204171626</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.description" type="integer">166393559</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.details" type="integer">198198907</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.alttitle" type="integer">82475009</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.description" type="integer">42715313</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.details" type="integer">54918453</label>
			<label index="emconf_conf.description" type="integer">49196456</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.alttitle" type="integer">43118947</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.description" type="integer">196469558</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.details" type="integer">238768833</label>
			<label index="emconf_locallang.alttitle" type="integer">182381040</label>
			<label index="emconf_locallang.description" type="integer">112585123</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.alttitle" type="integer">70637876</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.description" type="integer">207879145</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.alttitle" type="integer">155053783</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.description" type="integer">83027952</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.alttitle" type="integer">99552371</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.description" type="integer">88544755</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.alttitle" type="integer">190879862</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.description" type="integer">168628900</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.details" type="integer">76599956</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="tr" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="se" type="array">
			<label index="emconf_shy.alttitle" type="integer">217108965</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.description" type="integer">196807582</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.details" type="integer">206691994</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.alttitle" type="integer">61717939</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.description" type="integer">204987594</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.details" type="integer">149403635</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.alttitle" type="integer">6158334</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.description" type="integer">262753637</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.details" type="integer">54343024</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.alttitle" type="integer">174778315</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.description" type="integer">14159431</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.alttitle" type="integer">208790249</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.description" type="integer">261230598</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.alttitle" type="integer">222311525</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.description" type="integer">131352939</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.details" type="integer">16797237</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.alttitle" type="integer">8968835</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.description" type="integer">48322308</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.details" type="integer">170748201</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.alttitle" type="integer">252258090</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.description" type="integer">130243565</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.details" type="integer">78637286</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.alttitle" type="integer">26668595</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.description" type="integer">149991239</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.alttitle" type="integer">211801845</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.description" type="integer">225814359</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.details" type="integer">155805870</label>
			<label index=".alttitle" type="integer">194364373</label>
			<label index=".description" type="integer">17437649</label>
			<label index=".details" type="integer">238023326</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.alttitle" type="integer">75468930</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.description" type="integer">8590515</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.details" type="integer">183041250</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.alttitle" type="integer">102196861</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.description" type="integer">120757501</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.details" type="integer">92160698</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.alttitle" type="integer">121209022</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.description" type="integer">113056504</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.details" type="integer">179328140</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.alttitle" type="integer">262159324</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.description" type="integer">60133779</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.details" type="integer">201896892</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.alttitle" type="integer">234183730</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.description" type="integer">157844662</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.alttitle" type="integer">28332369</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.description" type="integer">93463627</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.details" type="integer">199359275</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.alttitle" type="integer">204171626</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.description" type="integer">166393559</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.details" type="integer">198198907</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.alttitle" type="integer">82475009</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.description" type="integer">42715313</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.details" type="integer">54918453</label>
			<label index="emconf_conf.description" type="integer">49196456</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.alttitle" type="integer">43118947</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.description" type="integer">196469558</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.details" type="integer">238768833</label>
			<label index="emconf_locallang.alttitle" type="integer">182381040</label>
			<label index="emconf_locallang.description" type="integer">112585123</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.alttitle" type="integer">70637876</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.description" type="integer">207879145</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.alttitle" type="integer">155053783</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.description" type="integer">83027952</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.alttitle" type="integer">99552371</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.description" type="integer">88544755</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.alttitle" type="integer">190879862</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.description" type="integer">168628900</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.details" type="integer">76599956</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="pt" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ru" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ro" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ch" type="array">
			<label index="emconf_shy.alttitle" type="integer">217108965</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.description" type="integer">196807582</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.details" type="integer">206691994</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.alttitle" type="integer">61717939</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.description" type="integer">204987594</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.details" type="integer">149403635</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.alttitle" type="integer">6158334</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.description" type="integer">262753637</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.details" type="integer">54343024</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.alttitle" type="integer">174778315</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.description" type="integer">14159431</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.alttitle" type="integer">208790249</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.description" type="integer">261230598</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.alttitle" type="integer">222311525</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.description" type="integer">131352939</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.details" type="integer">16797237</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.alttitle" type="integer">8968835</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.description" type="integer">48322308</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.details" type="integer">170748201</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.alttitle" type="integer">252258090</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.description" type="integer">130243565</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.details" type="integer">78637286</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.alttitle" type="integer">26668595</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.description" type="integer">149991239</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.alttitle" type="integer">211801845</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.description" type="integer">225814359</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.details" type="integer">155805870</label>
			<label index=".alttitle" type="integer">194364373</label>
			<label index=".description" type="integer">17437649</label>
			<label index=".details" type="integer">238023326</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.alttitle" type="integer">75468930</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.description" type="integer">8590515</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.details" type="integer">183041250</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.alttitle" type="integer">102196861</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.description" type="integer">120757501</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.details" type="integer">92160698</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.alttitle" type="integer">121209022</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.description" type="integer">113056504</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.details" type="integer">179328140</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.alttitle" type="integer">262159324</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.description" type="integer">60133779</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.details" type="integer">201896892</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.alttitle" type="integer">234183730</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.description" type="integer">157844662</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.alttitle" type="integer">28332369</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.description" type="integer">93463627</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.details" type="integer">199359275</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.alttitle" type="integer">204171626</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.description" type="integer">166393559</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.details" type="integer">198198907</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.alttitle" type="integer">82475009</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.description" type="integer">42715313</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.details" type="integer">54918453</label>
			<label index="emconf_conf.description" type="integer">49196456</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.alttitle" type="integer">43118947</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.description" type="integer">196469558</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.details" type="integer">238768833</label>
			<label index="emconf_locallang.alttitle" type="integer">182381040</label>
			<label index="emconf_locallang.description" type="integer">112585123</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.alttitle" type="integer">70637876</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.description" type="integer">207879145</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.alttitle" type="integer">155053783</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.description" type="integer">83027952</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.alttitle" type="integer">99552371</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.description" type="integer">88544755</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.alttitle" type="integer">190879862</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.description" type="integer">168628900</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.details" type="integer">76599956</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="sk" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="lt" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="is" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="hr" type="array">
			<label index="emconf_shy.alttitle" type="integer">217108965</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.description" type="integer">196807582</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.details" type="integer">206691994</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.alttitle" type="integer">61717939</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.description" type="integer">204987594</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.details" type="integer">149403635</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.alttitle" type="integer">6158334</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.description" type="integer">262753637</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.details" type="integer">54343024</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.alttitle" type="integer">174778315</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.description" type="integer">14159431</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.alttitle" type="integer">208790249</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.description" type="integer">261230598</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.alttitle" type="integer">222311525</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.description" type="integer">131352939</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.details" type="integer">16797237</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.alttitle" type="integer">8968835</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.description" type="integer">48322308</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.details" type="integer">170748201</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.alttitle" type="integer">252258090</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.description" type="integer">130243565</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.details" type="integer">78637286</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.alttitle" type="integer">26668595</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.description" type="integer">149991239</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.alttitle" type="integer">211801845</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.description" type="integer">225814359</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.details" type="integer">155805870</label>
			<label index=".alttitle" type="integer">194364373</label>
			<label index=".description" type="integer">17437649</label>
			<label index=".details" type="integer">238023326</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.alttitle" type="integer">75468930</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.description" type="integer">8590515</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.details" type="integer">183041250</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.alttitle" type="integer">102196861</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.description" type="integer">120757501</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.details" type="integer">92160698</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.alttitle" type="integer">121209022</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.description" type="integer">113056504</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.details" type="integer">179328140</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.alttitle" type="integer">262159324</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.description" type="integer">60133779</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.details" type="integer">201896892</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.alttitle" type="integer">234183730</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.description" type="integer">157844662</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.alttitle" type="integer">28332369</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.description" type="integer">93463627</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.details" type="integer">199359275</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.alttitle" type="integer">204171626</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.description" type="integer">166393559</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.details" type="integer">198198907</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.alttitle" type="integer">82475009</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.description" type="integer">42715313</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.details" type="integer">54918453</label>
			<label index="emconf_conf.description" type="integer">49196456</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.alttitle" type="integer">43118947</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.description" type="integer">196469558</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.details" type="integer">238768833</label>
			<label index="emconf_locallang.alttitle" type="integer">182381040</label>
			<label index="emconf_locallang.description" type="integer">112585123</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.alttitle" type="integer">70637876</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.description" type="integer">207879145</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.alttitle" type="integer">155053783</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.description" type="integer">83027952</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.alttitle" type="integer">99552371</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.description" type="integer">88544755</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.alttitle" type="integer">190879862</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.description" type="integer">168628900</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.details" type="integer">76599956</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="hu" type="array">
			<label index="emconf_shy.alttitle" type="integer">217108965</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.description" type="integer">196807582</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.details" type="integer">206691994</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.alttitle" type="integer">61717939</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.description" type="integer">204987594</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.details" type="integer">149403635</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.alttitle" type="integer">6158334</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.description" type="integer">262753637</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.details" type="integer">54343024</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.alttitle" type="integer">174778315</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.description" type="integer">14159431</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.alttitle" type="integer">208790249</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.description" type="integer">261230598</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.alttitle" type="integer">222311525</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.description" type="integer">131352939</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.details" type="integer">16797237</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.alttitle" type="integer">8968835</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.description" type="integer">48322308</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.details" type="integer">170748201</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.alttitle" type="integer">252258090</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.description" type="integer">130243565</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.details" type="integer">78637286</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.alttitle" type="integer">26668595</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.description" type="integer">149991239</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.alttitle" type="integer">211801845</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.description" type="integer">225814359</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.details" type="integer">155805870</label>
			<label index=".alttitle" type="integer">194364373</label>
			<label index=".description" type="integer">17437649</label>
			<label index=".details" type="integer">238023326</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.alttitle" type="integer">75468930</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.description" type="integer">8590515</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.details" type="integer">183041250</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.alttitle" type="integer">102196861</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.description" type="integer">120757501</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.details" type="integer">92160698</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.alttitle" type="integer">121209022</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.description" type="integer">113056504</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.details" type="integer">179328140</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.alttitle" type="integer">262159324</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.description" type="integer">60133779</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.details" type="integer">201896892</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.alttitle" type="integer">234183730</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.description" type="integer">157844662</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.alttitle" type="integer">28332369</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.description" type="integer">93463627</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.details" type="integer">199359275</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.alttitle" type="integer">204171626</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.description" type="integer">166393559</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.details" type="integer">198198907</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.alttitle" type="integer">82475009</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.description" type="integer">42715313</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.details" type="integer">54918453</label>
			<label index="emconf_conf.description" type="integer">49196456</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.alttitle" type="integer">43118947</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.description" type="integer">196469558</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.details" type="integer">238768833</label>
			<label index="emconf_locallang.alttitle" type="integer">182381040</label>
			<label index="emconf_locallang.description" type="integer">112585123</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.alttitle" type="integer">70637876</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.description" type="integer">207879145</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.alttitle" type="integer">155053783</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.description" type="integer">83027952</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.alttitle" type="integer">99552371</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.description" type="integer">88544755</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.alttitle" type="integer">190879862</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.description" type="integer">168628900</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.details" type="integer">76599956</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="gl" type="array">
			<label index="emconf_shy.alttitle" type="integer">217108965</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="th" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="gr" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="hk" type="array">
			<label index="emconf_shy.alttitle" type="integer">217108965</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.description" type="integer">196807582</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.details" type="integer">206691994</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.alttitle" type="integer">61717939</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.description" type="integer">204987594</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.details" type="integer">149403635</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.alttitle" type="integer">6158334</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.description" type="integer">262753637</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.details" type="integer">54343024</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.alttitle" type="integer">174778315</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.description" type="integer">14159431</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.alttitle" type="integer">208790249</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.description" type="integer">261230598</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.alttitle" type="integer">222311525</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.description" type="integer">131352939</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.details" type="integer">16797237</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.alttitle" type="integer">8968835</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.description" type="integer">48322308</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.details" type="integer">170748201</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.alttitle" type="integer">252258090</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.description" type="integer">130243565</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.alttitle" type="integer">26668595</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.description" type="integer">149991239</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.alttitle" type="integer">211801845</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.description" type="integer">225814359</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.details" type="integer">155805870</label>
			<label index=".alttitle" type="integer">194364373</label>
			<label index=".description" type="integer">17437649</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.alttitle" type="integer">75468930</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.description" type="integer">8590515</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.alttitle" type="integer">102196861</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.description" type="integer">120757501</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.alttitle" type="integer">121209022</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.description" type="integer">113056504</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.alttitle" type="integer">262159324</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.description" type="integer">60133779</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.details" type="integer">201896892</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.alttitle" type="integer">234183730</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.description" type="integer">157844662</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.alttitle" type="integer">28332369</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.description" type="integer">93463627</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.details" type="integer">199359275</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.alttitle" type="integer">204171626</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.description" type="integer">166393559</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.details" type="integer">198198907</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.alttitle" type="integer">82475009</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.description" type="integer">42715313</label>
			<label index="emconf_conf.description" type="integer">49196456</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.alttitle" type="integer">43118947</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.description" type="integer">196469558</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.details" type="integer">238768833</label>
			<label index="emconf_locallang.alttitle" type="integer">182381040</label>
			<label index="emconf_locallang.description" type="integer">112585123</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.alttitle" type="integer">70637876</label>
			<label index="emconf_moduleNames.description" type="integer">207879145</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.alttitle" type="integer">155053783</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.description" type="integer">83027952</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.alttitle" type="integer">99552371</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.description" type="integer">88544755</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.alttitle" type="integer">190879862</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.description" type="integer">168628900</label>
			<label index="emconf_NSerrors.details" type="integer">76599956</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="eu" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="bg" type="array">
			<label index="emconf_shy.alttitle" type="integer">217108965</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.description" type="integer">196807582</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.details" type="integer">206691994</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.alttitle" type="integer">61717939</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.description" type="integer">204987594</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.details" type="integer">149403635</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.alttitle" type="integer">6158334</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.description" type="integer">262753637</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.details" type="integer">54343024</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.alttitle" type="integer">174778315</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.description" type="integer">14159431</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.alttitle" type="integer">208790249</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.description" type="integer">261230598</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.alttitle" type="integer">222311525</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.description" type="integer">131352939</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.details" type="integer">16797237</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.alttitle" type="integer">8968835</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.description" type="integer">48322308</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.details" type="integer">170748201</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.alttitle" type="integer">252258090</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.description" type="integer">130243565</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.alttitle" type="integer">26668595</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.description" type="integer">149991239</label>
			<label index=".alttitle" type="integer">194364373</label>
			<label index=".description" type="integer">17437649</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.alttitle" type="integer">75468930</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.alttitle" type="integer">102196861</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.alttitle" type="integer">121209022</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.description" type="integer">113056504</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.alttitle" type="integer">262159324</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.alttitle" type="integer">28332369</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.alttitle" type="integer">204171626</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.alttitle" type="integer">82475009</label>
			<label index="emconf_TSfiles.alttitle" type="integer">43118947</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.alttitle" type="integer">155053783</label>
			<label index="emconf_classNames.description" type="integer">83027952</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.alttitle" type="integer">99552371</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="br" type="array">
			<label index="emconf_shy.alttitle" type="integer">217108965</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.description" type="integer">196807582</label>
			<label index="emconf_shy.details" type="integer">206691994</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.alttitle" type="integer">61717939</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.description" type="integer">204987594</label>
			<label index="emconf_category.details" type="integer">149403635</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.alttitle" type="integer">6158334</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.description" type="integer">262753637</label>
			<label index="emconf_dependencies.details" type="integer">54343024</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.alttitle" type="integer">174778315</label>
			<label index="emconf_conflicts.description" type="integer">14159431</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.alttitle" type="integer">208790249</label>
			<label index="emconf_priority.description" type="integer">261230598</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.alttitle" type="integer">222311525</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.description" type="integer">131352939</label>
			<label index="emconf_module.details" type="integer">16797237</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.alttitle" type="integer">8968835</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.description" type="integer">48322308</label>
			<label index="emconf_state.details" type="integer">170748201</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.alttitle" type="integer">252258090</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.description" type="integer">130243565</label>
			<label index="emconf_internal.details" type="integer">78637286</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.alttitle" type="integer">26668595</label>
			<label index="emconf_clearCacheOnLoad.description" type="integer">149991239</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.alttitle" type="integer">211801845</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.description" type="integer">225814359</label>
			<label index="emconf_modify_tables.details" type="integer">155805870</label>
			<label index=".alttitle" type="integer">194364373</label>
			<label index=".description" type="integer">17437649</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.alttitle" type="integer">75468930</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.description" type="integer">8590515</label>
			<label index="emconf_private.details" type="integer">183041250</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.alttitle" type="integer">102196861</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.description" type="integer">120757501</label>
			<label index="emconf_download_password.details" type="integer">92160698</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.alttitle" type="integer">121209022</label>
			<label index="emconf_type.description" type="integer">113056504</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.alttitle" type="integer">262159324</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.description" type="integer">60133779</label>
			<label index="emconf_doubleInstall.details" type="integer">201896892</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.alttitle" type="integer">234183730</label>
			<label index="emconf_rootfiles.description" type="integer">157844662</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.alttitle" type="integer">28332369</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.description" type="integer">93463627</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbReq.details" type="integer">199359275</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.alttitle" type="integer">204171626</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.description" type="integer">166393559</label>
			<label index="emconf_dbStatus.details" type="integer">198198907</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.alttitle" type="integer">82475009</label>
			<label index="emconf_flags.description" type="integer">42715313</label>
			<label index="emconf_errors.alttitle" type="integer">99552371</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="et" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ar" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="he" type="array">
			<label index="emconf_category.alttitle" type="integer">61717939</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ua" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="lv" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="jp" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="vn" type="array">
		</languageKey>
	</orig_hash>
</T3locallang>