<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
	<meta type="array">
		<description>CSH for Language Extension of htmlArea RTE</description>
		<type>CSH</type>
		<csh_table>xEXT_rtehtmlarea_Language</csh_table>
	</meta>
	<data type="array">
		<languageKey index="default" type="array">
			<label index=".alttitle">htmlArea RTE &gt; Language</label>
			<label index=".description">The Language feature allows to edit the language and text direction attributes of an element in the RTE editing area.</label>
			<label index=".details">The following items may appear in the RTE toolbar:
- a selector box that allows to assign the language of contents of an element;
- two buttons that allow to set the direction of text;
- another button that allows to make the language marks visible wittin the RTE editing area.
The language selector box may also appear in some dialogues along with a text direction selector box.</label>
			<label index=".image">EXT:rtehtmlarea/extensions/Language/skin/images/left_to_right.gif,
EXT:rtehtmlarea/extensions/Language/skin/images/right_to_left.gif,
EXT:rtehtmlarea/extensions/Language/skin/images/show-language-marks.gif</label>
			<label index=".image_descr">"Left to right" icon in the editor tool bar.
"Right to left" icon in the editor tool bar.
"Show language marks" icon in the editor tool bar.
</label>
			<label index=".seeAlso">xEXT_rtehtmlarea_Language:languageCombo,
xEXT_rtehtmlarea_Language:directionCombo,
</label>
			<label index="languageCombo.alttitle">Language of contents</label>
			<label index="languageCombo.description">Select the language of the contents of the element.</label>
			<label index="languageCombo.details">The language selector box may appear in the RTE toolbar and in some dialogues.
The selector shows the language currently assigned to the current element, if any.
Selecting a language assigns it to the element. If a language was already assigned to the element, it is replaced by the newly selected language.
Any currently assigned language may be removed by selecting the "Remove language mark" item at the top of the list of the selector box.</label>
			<label index="directionCombo.alttitle">Direction of text</label>
			<label index="directionCombo.description">Select the direction of text within the contents of the element.</label>
			<label index="directionCombo.details">The text direction selector box may appear in some dialogues.
The selector shows the direction of text currently set on the current element, if any.
Selecting a direction sets it on the element. If a direction was already set on the element, it is replaced by the newly selected direction.
Any currently set direction may be removed by selecting the "Not set" item at the top of the list of the selector box.</label>
		</languageKey>
	</data>
</T3locallang>
