<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
	<meta type="array">
		<description>CSH for Frontend Users</description>
		<type>CSH</type>
		<fileId>EXT:context_help/locallang_csh_fe_users.php</fileId>
		<csh_table>fe_users</csh_table>
		<labelContext type="array">
		</labelContext>
	</meta>
	<data type="array">
		<languageKey index="default" type="array">
			<label index="username.description">Enter the username of the website user. This is needed to login.</label>
			<label index="username.syntax">A username is required and must be in lowercase without spaces in it. Furthermore the username must be unique among other usernames in the page where it's saved. If it is not unique a number will be prepended automatically.</label>
			<label index="password.description">Enter the password for the username above. This is needed to login.</label>
			<label index="password.syntax">A password is required and must be in lowercase without spaces in it.</label>
			<label index="usergroup.description">Select a user group for the username.</label>
			<label index="usergroup.details">When a user logs in he is able to view all content which is access restricted to the user &lt;em&gt;group(s)&lt;/em&gt; the user is a member of. Therefore the user login primarily makes sense with regard to the member groups.</label>
			<label index="lockToDomain.description">Enter the host name from which the user is forced to login.</label>
			<label index="lockToDomain.details">A TYPO3 system may have multiple domains pointing to it. Therefore this option secures that users can login only from a certain host name.</label>
			<label index="lockToDomain.syntax">Either a domain name, &quot;www.typo3.com&quot; or an IP address, &quot;10.34.222.83&quot;</label>
			<label index="_lockToDomain.seeAlso">fe_groups:lockToDomain</label>
			<label index="name.description">Enter the regular name of the user, both first- and surname.</label>
			<label index="address.description">Enter the street address of the user.</label>
			<label index="www.description">Enter the homepage URL</label>
			<label index="title.description">Enter the job title, eg. 'Director' or 'Accountant'.</label>
			<label index="company.description">Enter the name of the company in which the user is employed.</label>
			<label index="image.description">Insert a photo of the user.</label>
			<label index="disable.description">This option will temporarily disable the user from logging in.</label>
			<label index="_disable.seeAlso">fe_users:starttime,fe_users:endtime</label>
			<label index="starttime.description">Enter the date from which the account is active.</label>
			<label index="starttime.syntax">The syntax is dd-mm-yy, but you can just enter a &quot;d&quot; in the field to insert todays date. Or &quot;d+10&quot; to insert the date 10 days from now etc. 
The field will re-format any input to fit the format it understands so you can just experiment and you will be able to clearly see how dates should be entered.</label>
			<label index="_starttime.seeAlso">fe_users:disable,fe_users:endtime</label>
			<label index="endtime.description">Enter the date from which the account is disabled.</label>
			<label index="endtime.syntax">See &quot;Start&quot;</label>
			<label index="_endtime.seeAlso">fe_users:disable,fe_users:starttime</label>
			<label index="TSconfig.description">Enter additional TSconfig for the user (advanced).</label>
			<label index="TSconfig.details">This field allows you to enter TypoScript style configuration values for the user. Currently there are no system defined keys. If there ever will be, they will be described in detail in the administrative documentation.

The primary use of this field (as well as the 'sister'-field in the Website usergroup table) is for custom purposes. In this case, you should use the root-key &quot;user&quot; for your customly defined values. Thus you don't risk any future system keys to interfere with your configuration.

You access the values of the configuration from your frontend plugins by calling the function &lt;em&gt;$GLOBALS[&quot;TSFE&quot;]-&gt;fe_user-&gt;getUserTSconf()&lt;/em&gt; which will return an array with the valuetree in it.

&lt;b&gt;Warning:&lt;/b&gt; You should use Website user/group TSconfig in your PHP-scripts ONLY if your resulting content is NOT being cached! So call it from TypoScript USER_INT cObjects or disable caching from your PHP-code by calling &lt;em&gt;$GLOBALS[&quot;TSFE&quot;]-&gt;set_no_cache();&lt;/em&gt;

&lt;b&gt;TSconfig from Website usergroups:&lt;/b&gt;
Notice that the configuration from the field TSconfig in the member groups of the user is accumulated and prepended to the TSconfig of the user before it's parsed. This means for instance that a key defined in the TSconfig of the user (this field) will override the same key defined in the last (bottom) usergroup in the list which will again override the same key defined in the first (top) usergroup in the list.

&lt;b&gt;Example:&lt;/b&gt;
Let's imagine you want to define for a user that his name is printed in the bottom of the webpages when he is logged in. First of all you must write a PHP-function and insert the result from it as a USER_INT cObject in the bottom of the page. But your function needs to know, whether or not this user is configured to have his name printed. So you decide to use a custom TSconfig key, 'user.printUserName':

&lt;em&gt;In the TSconfig field of the user or usergroup:&lt;/em&gt;

user.printUserName = 1


&lt;em&gt;In your PHP-function:&lt;/em&gt;

$userTSConfig = $GLOBALS[&quot;TSFE&quot;]-&gt;fe_user-&gt;getUserTSconf();
if ($userTSConfig[&quot;user.&quot;][&quot;printUserName&quot;]) {
  return $GLOBALS[&quot;TSFE&quot;]-&gt;fe_user-&gt;user[&quot;name&quot;];
}</label>
			<label index="TSconfig.syntax">TypoScript syntax, without conditions and constants.</label>
			<label index="_TSconfig.seeAlso">TSconfig for TSFE | http://typo3.org/documentation/document-library/doc_core_tsconfig/TCEMAIN/
pages:TSconfig,
fe_groups:TSconfig,
be_users:TSconfig,
be_groups:TSconfig</label>
			<label index=".description">A website login user.</label>
			<label index=".details">This is users with a username and password who are allowed specific access to otherwise restricted areas on your website.</label>
			<label index="_.seeAlso">fe_groups
be_users</label>
			<label index="_username.seeAlso">Creating Frontend Users and Groups | http://typo3.org/documentation/document-library/doc_tut_quickstart/Create_users_group/</label>
			<label index="_username.image"></label>
			<label index="_.image">EXT:context_help/cshimages/feusers_1.png,
EXT:context_help/cshimages/feusers_2.png,</label>
			<label index=".image_descr">Part of the form for editing a frontend user.
A typical login box (standard) on the website where frontend users can login.</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="dk" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="de" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="no" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="it" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="fr" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="es" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="nl" type="array">
			<label index="username.description">Voer de gebruikersnaam van de website gebruiker in. Dit is nodig om in te loggen.</label>
			<label index="username.syntax">Een gebruikersnaam is verplicht en moet worden geschreven in kleine letters en zonder spaties. De gebruikersnaam moet uniek zijn op de pagina waar deze wordt opgeslagen. Wanneer de naam niet uniek is wordt er automatisch een nummer toegevoegd.</label>
			<label index="password.description">Voer het wachtwoord in voor deze gebruikersnaam. Dit is nodig om in te loggen.</label>
			<label index="password.syntax">Een wachtwoord is verplicht, moet in lowercase en zonder spaties worden geschreven.</label>
			<label index="usergroup.description">Selecteer een gebruikersgroep voor de gebruiker.</label>
			<label index="usergroup.details">Wanneer een gebruiker inlogd kan hij alle inhoud zien waarvan de toegang beperkt is tot de &lt;em&gt;gebruikersgroep(en)&lt;/em&gt; waar de gebruiker lid van is. ???</label>
			<label index="lockToDomain.description">Voer de hostnaam in waarvoor de gebruiker moet inloggen.</label>
			<label index="lockToDomain.details">Meerdere domeinen kunnen naar een TYPO3 systeem verwijzen. Deze optie maakt het mogelijk dat een gebruiker alleen op een specifiek domein kan inloggen.</label>
			<label index="lockToDomain.syntax">Een domeinnaam, &quot;www.typo3.com&quot; of een IP-adres, &quot;10.34.222.83&quot;</label>
			<label index="name.description">Voer de naam in van de gebruiker, zowel voor- als achternaam</label>
			<label index="address.description">Voer het postadres in van de gebruiker</label>
			<label index="www.description">Voer de homepage URL van de gebruiker in</label>
			<label index="title.description">Voer de functie van de gebruiker in, bijv: &quot;Directeur&quot; of &quot;Accountant&quot;</label>
			<label index="company.description">Voer de naam van de werkgever van de gebruiker in</label>
			<label index="image.description">Voeg een foto van de gebruiker toe.</label>
			<label index="disable.description">Deze optie schakelt de mogelijkheid om in te loggen tijdelijk uit.</label>
			<label index="starttime.description">Voer een startdatum voor dit account in.</label>
			<label index="starttime.syntax">[SHARED:dateTime]</label>
			<label index="endtime.description">Voer een datum in waarop het account wordt beëindigd.</label>
			<label index="endtime.syntax">[SHARED:dateTime]</label>
			<label index="TSconfig.description">Voer additionele TSconfig in voor deze gebruiker (geavanceerd)</label>
			<label index="TSconfig.details">Dit veld biedt de mogelijkheid om TypoScript configuratie informatie voor de gebruiker in te voeren. Op dit moment zijn er geen voorgedefinieerde sleutelwaarden. Wanneer deze beschikbaar komen, zullen ze worden beschreven in de Administrator documentatie.

Dit veld wordt (evenals het 'zuster-veld' in de website gebruikersgroep tabel) hoofdzakelijk gebruikt voor specifieke doeleinden. In dit geval moet je de root-sleutelwaarde &quot;user&quot; gebruiken voor je specifiek gedefinieerde waarden. Op die manier voorkom je dat mogelijk toekomstige systeem sleutelwaarde conflicteren met je eigen configuratie.

Je hebt toegang tot de waarden van de configuratie vanuit je PHP include code aan de voorzijde (frontend) door het aanroepen van de functie &lt;em&gt;$GLOBALS[&quot;TSFE&quot;]-&gt;fe_user-&gt;getUserTSconf()&lt;/em&gt;. Deze functie levert een array met de waardenboom.

&lt;b&gt;Waarschuwing:&lt;/b&gt; Je moet Website gebruiker(s)/groep TSconfig alleen in je PHP-scripts gebruiken als de resulterende inhoud niet wordt gecached! Roep het dus aan vanuit TypoScript USER_INT cObjects, of schakel het cachen uit in je PHP-code door het aanroepen van de functie: &lt;em&gt;$GLOBAL[&quot;TSFE&quot;]-&gt;set_no_cache();&lt;/em)

&lt;b&gt;TSConfig van Website gebruikersgroepen:&lt;/&lt;b&gt;
Let op dat de configuratie in het veld TSConfig in de groepen, waar de gebruiker lid van is, bovenaan wordt toegevoegd aan de TSConfig van de gebruiker voordat deze geparsed wordt. Dit betekent dat bijvoorbeeld dat een waarde die in de TSConfig van de gebruiker is gedefinieerd (dit veld) dezelfde waarde die in de laatste gebruikersgroep is gedefinieerd zal overschrijven. De laatste gedefinieerde waarde in de gebruikersgroepen zal ook eerder gedefinieerde waarden (hoger in de lijst) overschrijven.

&lt;b&gt;Voorbeeld:&lt;/b&gt;
Stel je voor dat je voor een gebruiker wil vastleggen dat zijn naam onderaan een pagina wordt weergegeven waneer hij is ingelogd.
Allereerst moet je dan een PHP-functie schrijven en het resultaat van die functie toevoegen als een USER_INT cObject onderaan de bladzijde. Maar deze functie moet weten of voor deze gebruiker de naam weergegeven moet worden. Daarom besluit je een eigen TSConfig waarde te gebruiken, 'user.PrintUserName':

&lt;em&gt;In het TSConfig veld van de gebruikersgroep:&lt;/em&gt;

user.PrintUserName = 1

&lt;em&gt;In je PHP-functie:&lt;/em&gt;

$userTSConfig = $GLOBALS[&quot;TSFE&quot;]-&gt;fe_user-&gt;getUserTSconf();
if ($userTSConfig[&quot;user.&quot;][&quot;printUserName&quot;]) {
return $GLOBALS[&quot;TSFE&quot;]-&gt;fe_user-&gt;user[&quot;name&quot;];
}</label>
			<label index="TSconfig.syntax">TypoScript syntaxis, zonder condities en constanten</label>
			<label index=".description">Een website login gebruiker</label>
			<label index=".details">Dit zijn gebruikers met een gebruikersnaam en wachtwoord, die toegang hebben tot gedeelten van de website waarvoor de toegang is beperkt.</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="cz" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="pl" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="si" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="fi" type="array">
			<label index="username.description">Anna websivuston käyttäjän käyttäjänimi. Tätä tarvitaan sisäänkirjoittautumiseen (login).</label>
			<label index="username.syntax">Käyttäjänimi on pakollinen.Sen tulee koostua pienistä kirjaimista ilman välilyöntejä. Lisäksi käyttäjänimen tulee olla yksilöllinen, ainakin sillasivulle jonne se talletetaan. Jos se ei ole yksilöllinen lisätään järjestysnumero automaattisesti.</label>
			<label index="password.description">Anna salasana ylläolevalle käyttäjänimelle. Tätä tarvitaan sisäänkirjoittautumiseen (login).</label>
			<label index="password.syntax">Salasana on pakollinen.Sen tulee koostua pienistä kirjaimista ilman välilyöntejä.</label>
			<label index="usergroup.description">Valitse käyttäjäryhmä käyttäjälle.</label>
			<label index="usergroup.details">Kun käyttäjä kirjoittautuu sisään on hänellä mahdollisuus nähdä kaikki sisältö johon pääsy on rajoitettu vain sille/niille käytäjä&lt;em&gt;ryhmälle/ryhmille&lt;/em&gt; joiden jäsen hän on. Näin ollen sissänkirjoittautumisessa on järkeä vain käyttäjäryhmiä käytettäessä.</label>
			<label index="lockToDomain.description">Anna se hostnimi (domain) johon käyttäjä on pakotettu kirjoittautuessaan sisään.</label>
			<label index="lockToDomain.details">TYPO3 järjestelmässä voi olla monta domainia. Siksi tämä vaihtoehto varmistaa käyttäjän pääsyn vain tiettyihin (sallittuihin) domaineihin.</label>
			<label index="lockToDomain.syntax">Anna domain nimi, esimerkiksi &quot;www.typo3.com&quot; tai IP osoite &quot;10.34.444.83&quot;</label>
			<label index="name.description">Anna käyttäjän oikea nimi, sekä etu- että sukunimi.</label>
			<label index="address.description">Anna käyttäjän soite.</label>
			<label index="www.description">Anna käyttäjän kotisivun URL.</label>
			<label index="title.description">Anna käyttäjän ammatti/arvo, esim. 'Tj&quot; tai &quot;suunnittelija&quot;.</label>
			<label index="company.description">Anna yrityksen nimi jossa käyttäjä työskentelee.</label>
			<label index="image.description">Anna käyttäjän kuva.</label>
			<label index="disable.description">Tämä vaihtoehto asettaa väliaikaisesti kiellon käyttäjän sisäänkirjoittautumiselle.</label>
			<label index="starttime.description">Anna päiväys josta alkaen käyttäjän tili on aktiivinen.</label>
			<label index="starttime.syntax">[SHARED:dateTime]</label>
			<label index="endtime.description">Anna päiväys josta alkaen käyttäjän tili on kielletty sisäänkirjoitukselta.</label>
			<label index="endtime.syntax">[SHARED:dateTime]</label>
			<label index="TSconfig.description">Anna TSconfig lisämääritteet käyttäjälle (laajennettu).</label>
			<label index="TSconfig.details">Tähän kenttään on Sinun mahdollista antaa käyttäjälle TypoScript tyylin konfiguraatio tiedot. Nykyisellään ei ole järjestelmän määrittelemiä avaintietoja. Jos niitä joskus tulee ne kuvataan yksityiskohtaisesti TYPO#n järjestelmähallinnan dokumenteissa.

Tämän kentän pääasiallinen tarkoitus (kuten sen 'sisar-tiedon websivuston käyttäjäryhmä taulussa) on kustomointi. Tässä tarkoituksessa, tulee Sinun juuren avainta &quot;user&quot; määrittelemillesi arvoille. Näin et vaaranna tulevia järjestelmän avaimia jotka haittaisivat järjestelmän toimintaa.

Voit käyttää konfiguroimiasi arvoja PHP include koodista edustatoiminnoissa kutsumalla &lt;em&gt;$GLOBALS[&quot;TSFE&quot;]-&gt;fe_user-&gt;getUserTSconf()&lt;/em&gt; joka palauttaa taulukon jossa on arvorakenne.

&lt;b&gt;Varoitus:&lt;/b&gt; Voit käyttää Websivuston käyttäjä/ryhmä TSconfigia PHP-skriptissä ainoastaan jos tulossisältö ei puskutoida välimuistiin! Joten kutsu sitä TypoScript USER_INT cObjects tai poista puskurointi PHP-koodillasi kutsumalla &lt;em&gt;$GLOBALS[&quot;TSFE&quot;]-&gt;set_no_cache();&lt;/em&gt;

&lt;b&gt;TSconfig Websivuston käyttäjäryhmistä:&lt;/b&gt;
Huomaa erityisesti: TSconfig kentän tiedot käyttäjäryhmistä, siis niistä joihin käyttäjä kuuluu, lisätään käyttäjän TSconfig tietoihin (perään) ennenkuin tiedot käsitellään. Tämä tarkoittaa esimerkiksi että avaimen tieto joka on määritelty käyttäjälle ohitetaan saman avaimentiedolla joka on käyttäjäryhmässä. Käyttäjäryhmien tiedoista käytetään priorisoidusti ylintä.

&lt;b&gt;Esimerkki&lt;/b&gt;
Kuvitellaan että haluat käyttäjän nimen tulostettavaksi kunkin sivun alalaitaan, joille hän on kirjoittautunut sisään. Ensin Sinun on kirjoitettava PHP-skripti ja vietä sen tulokset USER_INT cObjektina sivulle. Mutta funktiosi tulee tietää onko käyttäjälle konfiguroitu nimi, jotta se voidaan kirjoittaa. Joten päätät käyttää kustomoitua TSconfig avainta, &quot;user.printUserName&quot; :

&lt;em&gt;TSconfig käyttäjällä tai käyttäjäryhmässä:&lt;/em&gt;

user.printUserName = 1

&lt;em&gt;PHP-funktiossa:&lt;/em&gt;

$userTSConfig = $GLOBALS[&quot;TSFE&quot;]-&gt;fe_user-&gt;getUserTSconf();
if ($userTSConfig[&quot;user.&quot;][&quot;printUserName&quot;]) {
return $GLOBALS[&quot;TSFE&quot;]-&gt;fe_user-&gt;user[&quot;name&quot;];
}</label>
			<label index="TSconfig.syntax">TypoScript syntaksin mukaisesti, ilman ehtoja ja vakioita.</label>
			<label index=".description">Websivuston login (sisäänkirjoitus) käyttäjä.</label>
			<label index=".details">Tässä ovat käyttäjät käyttäjänimineen ja salasanoineen joilla on oikeudet päästä muuten rajoitetuille alueille websivustollasi.</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="tr" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="se" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="pt" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ru" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ro" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ch" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="sk" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="lt" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="is" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="hr" type="array">
			<label index="username.description">Unesite korisničko ime za korisnika web site-a. Ovo je potrebno za ulazak.</label>
			<label index="username.syntax">Zahtjeva se korisničko ime koje mora biti pisano malim slovima bez razmaka. Nadalje, korisničko ime mora biti jedinstveno među korisničkim imenima na stranici gdje je spremljeno. Ako nije jedinstveno, automatski ce mu biti dodan broj na kraju.</label>
			<label index="password.description">Unesite zaporku za gornje korisničko ime. Ovo je potrebno za ulazak.</label>
			<label index="password.syntax">Zahtjeva se zaporka koja mora biti pisana malim slovima i bez razmaka.</label>
			<label index="usergroup.description">Izaberite korisničku grupu za ovo korisničko ime.</label>
			<label index="usergroup.details">Kada se korisnik ulogira, može vidjeti sav sadržaj kojem je pristup zabranjen za korisnika &lt;em&gt;group(s)&lt;/em&gt; čiji je član. Stoga korisnički login primarno ima smisla ovsno o grupi kojoj pripada.</label>
			<label index="lockToDomain.description">Unesite ima računala sa kojeg je korisnik primoran na ulazak.</label>
			<label index="lockToDomain.details">TYPO3 sustav može imati višestruke domene. Stoga ova opcija osigurava da se korisnik može ulogirati samo sa određenog računala.</label>
			<label index="lockToDomain.syntax">Unesite ime domene, &quot;www.typo3.com&quot; ili IP addresu, &quot;10.34.222.83&quot;</label>
			<label index="name.description">Unesite normalno ime korisnika, i ime i prezime.</label>
			<label index="address.description">Unesite ulicu korisnika.</label>
			<label index="www.description">Unesite URL stranice.</label>
			<label index="title.description">Unesite zanimanje, npr. 'Direktor' or 'Službenik'.</label>
			<label index="company.description">Unesite ime firme u kojoj je korisnik zaposlen.</label>
			<label index="image.description">Umetnite fotografiju korisnika.</label>
			<label index="disable.description">Ova opcija će privremeno onemogućiti prijavu korisnika.</label>
			<label index="starttime.description">Unesite datum od kojeg je račun aktivan.</label>
			<label index="starttime.syntax">[SHARED:dateTime]</label>
			<label index="endtime.description">Unesite datum od kojeg je račun onemogućen.</label>
			<label index="endtime.syntax">[SHARED:dateTime]</label>
			<label index="TSconfig.description">Unesite dodatni TSconfig za korisnika (napredno)</label>
			<label index="TSconfig.details">Ovo polje vam omogućuje da unesete TypoScript konfiguraciju
stilova za korisnika. Trenutno nema sistemski definiranih ključeva.
Ako će ih ikada biti, bit će u detalje opisani u administrativnoj
dokumentaciji.

Glavna namjena ovog polja (kao i 'sestrinjskog' polja u tablici
korisničkih gupa web site-a) je za razne svrhe. U ovom slučaju
koristite korjenski ključ  &quot;user&quot; za  vaše definirane vrijednosti.
Tako ne riskirate da budući sistemski ključevi dođu u sukob sa
vašom konfiguracijom.

Vrijednostima konfiguracije pristupate iz vašeg PHP uključenog koda
u frontend-u pozivajući funkciju &lt;em&gt;$GLOBALS[&quot;TSFE&quot;]-&gt;fe_user-&gt;getUserTSconf()&lt;/em&gt;
koja će vratiti polje sa vrijednostima.

&lt;b&gt;Upozorenje:&lt;/b&gt;Website user/group TSconfig u vašim PHP
skriptama koristite SAMO ako rezultirajući sadržaj NIJE keširan.
Stoga ga pozivajte iz TypoScript USER_INT cObjects ili isključite
keširanje u vašem PHP kodu pozivajući &lt;em&gt;$GLOBALS[&quot;TSFE&quot;]-&gt;set_no_cache();&lt;/em&gt;

&lt;b&gt;TSconfig iz Website korisničkih grupa:&lt;/b&gt;
Primjetite da je konfiguracija iz polja TSconfig u grupama čiji je korisnik
član akumulirana i nadodana na TSconfig korisnika prije parsiranja.
To znači za primjer da će ključ definiran u TSconfig-u korisnika (ovo polje)
nadjačati isti ključ definiran u zadnjoj (dno) korisničkoj grupi na listi
a taj će nadjačati isti ključ definiran u prvoj (vrh) korisničkoj grupi
na listi.

&lt;b&gt;Primjer:&lt;/b&gt;
Zamislimo da želite za korisnika definirati da mu se ime ispisuje
na dnu stranice kad se ulogira. Prije svega morate napisati
PHP funkciju i iz nje umetnuti sadržaj kao USER_INT cObject na
dnu stranice. Ali vaša funkcija mora znati da li je taj korisnik
konfiguriran da mu se ispisuje ime ili ne. Stoga odlučujete koristiti
vlastiti TSconfig ključ, 'user.printUserName':

&lt;em&gt;U TSconfig polju korisnika ili grupe:&lt;/em&gt;

user.printUserName = 1


&lt;em&gt;U vašoj PHP-funkciji:&lt;/em&gt;

$userTSConfig = $GLOBALS[&quot;TSFE&quot;]-&gt;fe_user-&gt;getUserTSconf();
if ($userTSConfig[&quot;user.&quot;][&quot;printUserName&quot;]) {
return $GLOBALS[&quot;TSFE&quot;]-&gt;fe_user-&gt;user[&quot;name&quot;];
}</label>
			<label index="TSconfig.syntax">TypoScript sintaksa, bez uvjeta i konstanti</label>
			<label index=".description">Korisnik website-a</label>
			<label index=".details">Ovo su korisnici sa korisničkim imenom i zaporkom kojima je dozvoljen poseban pristup inače zabranjenim dijelovima website-a.</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="hu" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="gl" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="th" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="gr" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="hk" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="eu" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="bg" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="br" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="et" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ar" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="he" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ua" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="lv" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="jp" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="vn" type="array">
		</languageKey>
	</data>
	<orig_hash type="array">
		<languageKey index="dk" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="de" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="no" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="it" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="fr" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="es" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="nl" type="array">
			<label index="username.description" type="integer">107422140</label>
			<label index="username.syntax" type="integer">111768378</label>
			<label index="password.description" type="integer">10412940</label>
			<label index="password.syntax" type="integer">68458992</label>
			<label index="usergroup.description" type="integer">171809046</label>
			<label index="usergroup.details" type="integer">62585212</label>
			<label index="lockToDomain.description" type="integer">139426379</label>
			<label index="lockToDomain.details" type="integer">140149042</label>
			<label index="lockToDomain.syntax" type="integer">634244</label>
			<label index="name.description" type="integer">173302476</label>
			<label index="address.description" type="integer">268060602</label>
			<label index="www.description" type="integer">258941487</label>
			<label index="title.description" type="integer">45554969</label>
			<label index="company.description" type="integer">7843590</label>
			<label index="image.description" type="integer">222235094</label>
			<label index="disable.description" type="integer">36519200</label>
			<label index="starttime.description" type="integer">167831915</label>
			<label index="starttime.syntax" type="integer">128611683</label>
			<label index="endtime.description" type="integer">184097136</label>
			<label index="endtime.syntax" type="integer">128611683</label>
			<label index="TSconfig.description" type="integer">177543566</label>
			<label index="TSconfig.details" type="integer">148060720</label>
			<label index="TSconfig.syntax" type="integer">117035971</label>
			<label index=".description" type="integer">156302739</label>
			<label index=".details" type="integer">114236735</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="cz" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="pl" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="si" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="fi" type="array">
			<label index="username.description" type="integer">107422140</label>
			<label index="username.syntax" type="integer">111768378</label>
			<label index="password.description" type="integer">10412940</label>
			<label index="password.syntax" type="integer">68458992</label>
			<label index="usergroup.description" type="integer">171809046</label>
			<label index="usergroup.details" type="integer">62585212</label>
			<label index="lockToDomain.description" type="integer">139426379</label>
			<label index="lockToDomain.details" type="integer">140149042</label>
			<label index="lockToDomain.syntax" type="integer">634244</label>
			<label index="name.description" type="integer">173302476</label>
			<label index="address.description" type="integer">268060602</label>
			<label index="www.description" type="integer">258941487</label>
			<label index="title.description" type="integer">45554969</label>
			<label index="company.description" type="integer">7843590</label>
			<label index="image.description" type="integer">222235094</label>
			<label index="disable.description" type="integer">36519200</label>
			<label index="starttime.description" type="integer">167831915</label>
			<label index="starttime.syntax" type="integer">128611683</label>
			<label index="endtime.description" type="integer">184097136</label>
			<label index="endtime.syntax" type="integer">128611683</label>
			<label index="TSconfig.description" type="integer">177543566</label>
			<label index="TSconfig.details" type="integer">148060720</label>
			<label index="TSconfig.syntax" type="integer">117035971</label>
			<label index=".description" type="integer">156302739</label>
			<label index=".details" type="integer">114236735</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="tr" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="se" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="pt" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ru" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ro" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ch" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="sk" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="lt" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="is" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="hr" type="array">
			<label index="username.description" type="integer">107422140</label>
			<label index="username.syntax" type="integer">111768378</label>
			<label index="password.description" type="integer">10412940</label>
			<label index="password.syntax" type="integer">68458992</label>
			<label index="usergroup.description" type="integer">171809046</label>
			<label index="usergroup.details" type="integer">62585212</label>
			<label index="lockToDomain.description" type="integer">139426379</label>
			<label index="lockToDomain.details" type="integer">140149042</label>
			<label index="lockToDomain.syntax" type="integer">634244</label>
			<label index="name.description" type="integer">173302476</label>
			<label index="address.description" type="integer">268060602</label>
			<label index="www.description" type="integer">258941487</label>
			<label index="title.description" type="integer">45554969</label>
			<label index="company.description" type="integer">7843590</label>
			<label index="image.description" type="integer">222235094</label>
			<label index="disable.description" type="integer">36519200</label>
			<label index="starttime.description" type="integer">167831915</label>
			<label index="starttime.syntax" type="integer">128611683</label>
			<label index="endtime.description" type="integer">184097136</label>
			<label index="endtime.syntax" type="integer">128611683</label>
			<label index="TSconfig.description" type="integer">177543566</label>
			<label index="TSconfig.details" type="integer">148060720</label>
			<label index="TSconfig.syntax" type="integer">117035971</label>
			<label index=".description" type="integer">156302739</label>
			<label index=".details" type="integer">114236735</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="hu" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="gl" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="th" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="gr" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="hk" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="eu" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="bg" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="br" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="et" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ar" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="he" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="ua" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="lv" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="jp" type="array">
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="vn" type="array">
		</languageKey>
	</orig_hash>
</T3locallang>